在我车上野餐是什么意思?
What is this having-a-picnic shit in my car?
老婆不给亲热
Please, man, I'm not getting my sex at home.
吃东西你也管
Don't deny me this.
你每晚跟个美女睡觉
You sleep with a beautiful woman every night.
婚姻的意义是:
I'm married. That's what married means.
睡在一起 但不做爱
It means you sleep together, but you can't get none.
别弄脏我的宝车 可以吗?
Watch it with all that shit, all right?
那么 杯架在哪?
Look, where's your cup holders?
没杯架
- I don't have one. - You don't have one?
什么意思? 八万块钱的车 没杯架?
$80,000 for this car, and you ain't got no cup holder?
是十万五 这是世上最快的车之一
It's $105,000. This is one of the fastest production cars on the planet.
4秒就加速到60 是限量生产的
Zero to sixty in four seconds, sweetie. This is a limited edition.
的确是蛮有限的 没杯架 没后座
You damn right it's limited. No cup holder, no backseat.
这是辆二人座的老二车
It's a shiny dick with two chairs in it.
只是我们这两个龟蛋 搭个顺风车罢了
I guess we the balls just dragging the fuck along.
妈的 抱歉
Damn. Sorry.
- 去捡 - 我捡不到
- Get it. - I can't get down there.
你的引擎有毛病, 我的手才不要放下去
You got an engine floor up here. My shit won't go down in there.
去 把胸挺高 摇屁股
Go. Titty-titty, strutty-strutty.
去啊 叫他们流口水
Go on. Make them want it.
我又不是你的老婆要帮你 清理善后
I ain't your wife to be cleaning up after you.
听著 我的手伸不下去 进去就卡住了
Watch my hand. My shit can't get down there. It gets stuck.
- 之后会变成什么样? 之后就会扭成这样 - 去捡薯条
- You come up with this shit. - Get that fry.
这不是丹尼餐厅 不可以吃- -
This ain't no goddamn Denny's. Don't eat in my car.
我不去丹尼吃 我不喜欢 他们对我的服务态度
I wouldn't buy shit from Denny's. I don't like the way we been treated.
上钩了 杰克 让我们去扁那些痞子
They bit, Jack. Let's skank these fools.
你不是为薯条 是为了看女人
You ain't interested in the fry. You all up in that.
- 出来 - 妈的
- Get out of the car, man. - Shit.
- 干他妈的做什么? - 我们倒楣了一星期
- What the fuck? - Me and my team have had a big week...
下车
so just get the fuck out of the car.
妈的 你多重 350磅?
Damn. What are you weighing, 350?
我打赌你吃太多欧罗肥了
I bet you're a big chicken-eating motherfucker.
为何胖子老找上我?
- Get the fuck out. - I always get the big motherfuckers.
- 现在就出来 - 好 好
- Get out of the car now! - All right!
- 等一下 - 这很好笑
- Hold on. - Now this is some funny shit.
让我告诉你 你今天会多倒楣
Let me tell you how bad a day you're having.
你们在抢两个警察
You're jacking two cops.
我还是喜剧演员呢…而且是不入流的
Yeah? I'm a stand-up comedian, and I suck!
- 所以我要借你的车 - 我不是英雄
- That's why I need your car. - I ain't no Wesley Snipes.
我只是跟开著一辆招摇的
I just hang out with stupid-ass friends that drive stupid-ass cars...
…骚包车的一个 浑球朋友在一起
that attract a lot of motherfucking attention!
我该跳过去打烂你头
I need to jump over this car and smack you in your head.
- 你为了薯条跟我鬼叫 - 才不是这样
- You're arguing over a French fry! - It's not about the French fry!
是你不尊重他人的财产
It's about your lack of respect for other people's property!
- 喂 喂 - 闭嘴
- Shut the fuck up! - This shit is stupid.
真是笨猪头 等他妈的一下
Hold the fuck on!
你想被扁 来呀
You want something bad enough? Come get some!
你喜欢这样吗?
You like that shit?
从电影上学来的
Wesley Snipes, Passenger57.
给我点他妈的湿手巾
Now give me a motherfucking Handiwipe.
讲个笑话给我听 痞子
Let's hear one of those jokes, bitch.
片名：绝地战警
迈阿密
觉得如何? 蛮像真的吧
What do you think, guys? Looks like the real thing.
记得你的任务吗?
You remember your assignment?
我是诱饵
Yeah, I'm the decoy.
没错
Yes, you are.
你在干他妈的什么?
What the fuck you doing?
警局吗?
Hello. Police?
我刚看到一个警察在南迈阿密第一街中枪
I just saw a policeman shot on South Miami and First Street.
快来救命啊
Help, please.
各组警员注意 有警察中枪
All units, officer down.
三号警戒
Officer down. Respond code three.
全体动员
All units in the vicinity, respond and identify.
这是空中二号 我们封锁了现场
This is Air Unit Two. We've got a full perimeter.
有警察中枪 我们需要更多地面支援
Officer down. We need additional ground units.
这是空中三号 收到 嫌犯人数不详
Air Three, roger. Suspector suspects unknown.
各位 安全了
Gentlemen, it's clear.
有限进入 空中警察
我们进来了
We're inside.
- 我们进来了 - 你们有20分钟
- We're in. - You got 20 minutes.
他妈的墨西哥饼会害死我
Goddamn taco is gonna kill me.
你们还剩12分钟 快
Guys, you got 12minutes. Let's go.
警卫室
好了 我们进来了
Clear. We're in.
动作快点 我们只剩6分钟
Move your ass. We've got six minutes.
好了
Ready.
准备发射 发射
Ready to fire. Go!
发射
Fire!
- Clear. - Go.
快
Come on! Let's go! Get out of here! Move it!
妈的
Damn.
作了好梦吗?
Did you have sweet dreams?
你真淫猥
You're so nasty.
你老说要有品味的时光
You're always saying you want quality time.
现在有时光 你也够品味
Right now, I got the time and you damn sure got the quality.
- 来嘛 - 你知道吗?
- Come on now. - You know what it is?
我记不得上次一起睡著是何时
I can't remember the last time we fell asleep together.
宝贝 宝贝 那是工作 不得已呀
Baby, it's my job. It's what it requires.
早上做个爱就能让我 变成更棒的警察
I'm a better cop when I get some in the morning.
- 负担就不会那么重 - 负担留在裤裆里吧
- I feel lighter on my feet. - Keep it in your pants, baby.
小鬼来了
I hear three little Burnetts coming down the hall.
太残忍了 你把我像一只丧家之犬丢在这
That's cold. You're leaving me here like a humping dog.
宝贝
- Hi, baby boy. - Mommy.
- 爸 爸 - 怎么了?
- Boy, what's up? - Daddy!
学校有人说我长的怪
Dad, at school, people say I look weird.
他们说我耳朵看起来好好笑
They say my ears look funny.
我也是有一样的问题 我耳朵跟你一样
Boy, your daddy has that same problem. I got the ears.
但你知道吗? 但这耳朵是用来听问题的
You know what? They just out there for you to listen to people's problems.
你是天使 这是你的翅膀
You're an angel. These are your wings.
拍啊 拍啊
That's all.
詹姆士 停下来 脱掉冰鞋好吗?
James, stop. Would you take them off...
别让我去你的学校 我会逮捕校长的
Don't let me come down to school. I'll arrest the principal.
- 妈! - 怎么了?
- Mom! - What?
- 詹姆士老推我! - 谈论我儿子的耳朵
- James keeps pushing me! Quit it! - Talking about my boy's ears.
听你妈妈的话
Do what your mama said.
- 麦克叔来了 - 你好吗 麦克叔?
- Uncle Mike's in the house. - What's up, Uncle Mike?
- 兄弟 - 怎么样?
- Partner. - What's going on?
你看这个
Quincy, check it out.
你干嘛拿我的食物?
- Why did you take my food? - Hey, girl.
别吻我 我不知道你的嘴 昨晚去过哪里
Don't kiss me. I don't know where your lips were last night. Move.
你昨晚有约会吗?
Uncle Mike, did you have a date last night?
有约会
Did I!
让我告诉你 这女孩- -
- Let me tell you, boy. This girl was... - Hey!
别在我儿子面前说你那些风流事
Don't tell my son your sleazy sex stories.
我只跟你老公说那些风流事
I only tell your husband my sleazy sex stories.
也别跟他说 他会学坏的
I don't want him knowing about them either; gives him ideas.
你为什么又要害我? 我在陪孩子
Why you putting me in this? I'm with my babies.
行吗? 谢了
- Thank you. - Hello?
- 吃 快吃 - 没问题
- Eat. Go on, girl. - No problem.
- 这是麦克 - 要我帮你擦嘴吗?
- You're on the mike with Mike. - Want Daddy to wipe your mouth?
队长 我想你是说"快滚过来"
I think you mean to say, "Get our asses down there, please, " Captain.
也许不是
- Now! - Maybe not.
宝贝
What's up, boy?
豪尔呢?
- Hey, baby! - Hey, Francine. Where's Howard?
他在找你而且心情不太好
He's down there. He's looking for you. He's been in better moods.
妈的
Damn.
快去办 妈的
Get it done, goddamn it.
欢迎参观恶梦
Welcome to our nightmare, boys.
看到没? 有什么不对吗?
See this? What's wrong with this picture?
记得这房间吗?
Remember this room?
这地方很眼熟吧?
Don't these flats look familiar?
这应有些像银砖一样的东西
There were these silver packets. They looked like bricks.
上面有红标签 大概有这么高吧?
Little red tags on them, about so high.
所有的海洛英都不见了
- All that heroin is gone. - This was our career bust...
这是我们事业上最英勇的事绩 值一亿美元吧?
worth $100 million.
- 不见了 - 真糟糕
- Gone. - This is bad.
我的意思是 这叫"完蛋了"
No, let me call it what it is. This is fucked up.
- 没错 探长 - 艾莉森 你好
- You got that right, detective. - Hello, Alison.
这是辛克莱组长 警纪组红人
You guys know Captain Sinclair, Internal Affairs' top watchdog.
如果我不认识你 我会以为 这是恭维
I'd actually take that as a compliment if I didn't know you so well.
对不起 如果你们要针锋相对 我不打扰- -
Excuse me, but if you two want to get personal, I could step out...
没什么针锋相对 我只是在执行任务
There's nothing personal here. I'm just doing my job.
我想知道一个…
I love knowing that one leak...
…一个能让媒体争相报导的头条
one headline could turn this nightmare into a media frenzy.
不会 我们在那之前会追回毒品的
That won't happen. We'll get the dope back before that ever happens.
好 从局里开始查
Good. Start by looking right here.
一定是内奸干的,我会查明的
This had to be an inside job, and I'll find out about it.
山契斯 洛斯 你们迟到了
Sanchez, Ruiz, you're late.
这是为了散发毒气用的?
Somebody put this in for toxic drug fumes.
好聪明的设计
Yeah, this was a brilliant design.
非常聪明 我喜欢
This was really intelligent. I like this.
我没有问他的感觉 我只想问他看见什么?
I didn't ask how he feels. I said, "What did he see?
他知道什么?
What does he know?"
你昨晚在哪?
Where were y'all last night?
叫你们的亲戚把毒品找回来 所以我们可以安枕而眠
Have your cousins bring the shit back, and we can all get some sleep.
本来是要这么做的 但有点麻烦
We were gonna do that, but we came up with a problem.
毒品被你妈吸光了
Your mama snorted up all the dope.
你们俩个过来
You two, get over there.
欧非没事 但他没有 任何线索可以告诉我们的
O'Fee will be all right, but he's got nothing to tell us.
他们杀诱饵让警方全员出动 非常聪明
So they kill a decoy, it empties the station. Very smart.
若杀真条子 警局会紧追不放
But they don't kill a real cop because they had the whole force on their ass.
这本来是你们的案子 你们继续追查
This was your case. You're back on it.
山契斯 洛斯 尽力支援他们所需
Sanchez, Ruiz, you back them up with whatever they need.
闭住狗嘴
- Shut your mouths. - But wait a second.
等等 本来是卡瑞拉的货
It was Carrera's drugs in the first place.
他在牢里被杀
But it couldn't have been him because he was killed in prison.
他同伙如何?
What about the rest of his crew?
那些白痴干不了这事
Those idiots don't have the precision to do this, but...
为了谨慎起见 去查一下
just in case I'm wrong, you check them out.
他们会用乌兹枪把欧非打烂
They'd have been up here with Uzis, splashing O'Fee all over the place.
聪明人才会干的案子
Takes a lot of brains to pull this off.
- 还有胆子 - 胆子是什么意思?
- Big cojones too. - What the hell are you talking about?
要解释那需要很久的时间
It would take me a month to explain to you what cojones is.
你们人在迈阿密 你们连胆子都不知道?
- You're in Miami. You don't know... - In English.
我们什么线索都没有 怎么回事? 我们什么线索都没有
What's the matter with you? We've got nothing!
干这事的人自己清楚得很
The guy who pulled this off knew what he was doing...
他什么都没留下 除了"干你娘"之外
and he left us nothing but a big "Fuck you."
洛斯 山契斯 …去查是谁装的通风管 立刻
Find out who installed the ventilating system. Do that now.
- 好冷酷 - 你妈妈的床也是
- That's cold. - Yeah, so is your mama's bed.
这一定是内奸干的
This could definitely be an inside job. Don't rule it out.
我觉得在三天内 调查局和药物管理局…
We've got 72 hours before the FBI and the DEA...
…会来接手这案子 我们会变成坏人
walk in here and shut us down, and we'll be the bad guys.
政策需要我们来扛这责任
Politics demand that somebody take the rap for this.
做你该做的 但动作要快
It's going to be us. Just do what you do, only faster.
乔乔
Jo jo, what's up?
还干化学家呀? 还在混合毒品吧?
You're still a chemist, right? Cutting drugs and shit like that?
我不知道 我不搞毒品了
I don't know nothing about that. I'm out of the drug business.
你知道吧
- You know something. - You don't know nothing?
我不搞毒了
I just said no to drugs.
- 不搞毒 那你搞什么? - 橡胶
- What are you into, Jo? - I'm into rubber.
你卖轮胎?
- You're selling tires? - Yeah.
- 你什么都不知道? 乔乔什么都不知道 - 我知道轮胎
- Jo jo don't know nothing. - Nothing. I know tires.
- 你说的是实话? - 我会骗你吗?
- You're telling me the truth? - Would I lie to you?
喂 你开车
- Would you lie to me? - I'm driving.
这是浪费时间
- Man, this is a waste of time. - Come on.
告诉你 在玛克丝的行业里 她真的很神通广大
In Max's line of work, she definitely gets the 411.
玛克丝 我怎么会知道你在这儿呀?
Maxi! How did I know I would find you up in here?
我要跟你谈谈 哪可以说话?
We have to talk. Is there someplace we can go?
装备室?
Yeah. Equipment room?
- 好好待著 - 好
- Behave your self. - I'm cool.
听著 我又得找你帮忙
Listen, I need some help, again.
还有什么新鲜事?
What else is new?
警局出了大麻烦
Major ill shit happened down at the police department.
关系著一大堆毒品和钱
There's a lot of hero in involved. There will be a lot of cash involved.
那些人会想找找乐子
There will definitely be some jolly young men who want to party.
你要什么?
What do you need?
很多人会跟你说 不会跟我说
A lot of people will talk to you that won't talk to me.
你是说客人?
You mean customers?
别冒险
I'm not asking you to get into any wild shit.
- 听到什么就通知我 - 我想我会
- Just call me if you hear something. - I think I will call you.
你在干嘛?
What the hell are you doing?
练速度
Trying to keep my shit quick.
哦对了,在家没做爱
That's right. You ain't getting none at home.
的确精力过剩 慢慢消耗吧
You got extra energy. Go ahead. Burn it off, baby.
有消息吗 法兰欣?
We got anything, Francine?
山契斯说冷气合约书…
Sanchez says the air-conditioning contract went...
…是属于比思坎湾的曼纽隆南的
to Manuel Arrona of Key Biscayne.
本周他在家工作 这是电话
He's working out of his house this week. That's the number.
他不在
He's not answering.
我们走吧
I guess we should just leave.
白白跑来这高级住宅区?
What? Make a trip all the way down here to high society for nothing?
那就是窗户的作用
That's why they have windows.
- 我们可以偷看 - 没关系
- We can peek in. - Yeah, that should do it.
- 我跌跤了 - 门自己开了?
- I tripped. - The handle just opened?
就在我跌跤之后 门自己开了
Right after I tripped, it just opened.
我猜这表示能进去了 看一下
I guess they want us to come in, take a peek.
有人在吗?
Hello?
我是你们的新邻居
We're your new neighbors.
别紧张 咱们是黑人
Don't be alarmed. We're Negroes.
不 兄弟 你的音太沉了
Man, there's too much bass in your voice.
会吓到白人的 应该这样说:
That scares white folks. You've got to sound like them.
我们可以借点黑砂糖吗?
We were wondering if we could borrow some brown sugar?
- 你放屁? - 没有
- You fart? - No, man.
死人
Dead guy.
好歹也算有人在家
Looks like somebody's home.
我假设一下
Let me take a stab at this one.
他卖通风管的蓝图给坏蛋
He sells the ventilation plans to the bad guys.
- 发了财 但死了 - 说的不错
- He gets rich, but he gets dead. - You're right on that one.
我打给刑事组
- I'll go call Homicide. - Whoa. Wait.
干嘛看到尸体就那样?
Why do you act like this every time we're around a dead body?
没事 我只是…
It's cool. I just...
拜托? 去查看一下
Please, look around.
那味道不太好闻
The smell and the fumes...
没想到
It's just unexpected, that's all.
看起来隆南老兄是个赌鬼
Looks like our buddy Arrona was a bit of a gambler.
赌狗 手球…
He's got dog track, jai alai.
需要那些钱还债
Probably needed the money to pay off his debts.
组头
Bookie.
妈的
- Whoops. - Damn, man.
不要乱碰死人脚
Watch where you're swinging a dead leg.
我的错
My bad.
妈的 我打给刑事组
Damn this. I'm calling Homicide.
我是毒品管制条子
I'm a narcotics cop.
死人是…
Dead bodies.
…开不了口了
Dead ends.
蛆
Maggots.
- 怎么了? - 我有点…
- What's wrong with you? - A little nauseous...
…想吐
I'm gonna...
去吃点墨西哥肉饼吧
What do you say we grab a couple burritos?
你开车开的跟阿婆一样
You drive almost slow enough to drive Miss Daisy.
买卖已完成了
Man, the transaction is done, all right?
一点线索也没 这次完了
- We ain't got shit, so it's over. - Relax.
以前找得出 这次也行
We got it before. We'll get it again.
你胸有成竹 是不是?
Yeah, you got it all figured out, don't you?
要有信心 玩家
You got to have faith, player.
还没找到之前 就被炒鱿鱼了
By the time we figured out how, we'd be out of a job.
省省吧 局里每个人 都要被炒鱿鱼
No, scratch that. Everybody in the damn unit will be out of a job.
但放心 他们觉得麦克拉瑞准没事
But don't worry. They tend to think Mike Lowrey will be all right.
而且他们以为你这富家公子 当条子是好玩的
Especially since they think you some rich kid playing cop.
我老子没留钱给我
Look, man, I ain't got no trust fund.
我没工作就没饭吃
For me: No job, no check.
局里其它人都是这样 至少大部分的人都是
That's like all the other guys in the unit. Most of us.
我当条子是好玩的?
So I'm playing cop now?
这是个游戏? 我是闹著玩的?
This is a game. I'm just joking around.
你老爱当"超级警探"
You always wanted to be Starsky or Hutch.
你知道吗? 我听够你这屁话了
Know what? I'm so sick of this bullshit.
我家里留钱给我 我该道歉吗?
I'm supposed to apologize for my family leaving me money?
我一心只想当条子
All I ever wanted to be was a cop.
我天天付出所有心力
I get up early and take it to the max every day.
我是第一个到案发现场 最后一个离开的
I'm the first guy through the door and the last to leave the crime scene...
知道吗? 你们都去死 干
so fuck you and fuck them...
谁对我不爽都去死
and fuck everybody who got a problem with Mike Lowrey.
- 我爱你 - 干 马可士
- I love you, man. - Fuck you, Marcus.
真的 你很棒 你是我搭档
I do. You're cool with me. You're my partner.
- 闭嘴 - 阿婆司机
Shut up. Slow-ass driver.
- 开车像个娘们似的 - 我干嘛要那样?
- Driving like a bitch. - Why I got to be all that?
娘娘腔
- Slow-ass Miss Daisy. - I'll take me and you off this cliff...
你再骂 我就开到悬崖下
you keep fucking with me.
那么海里就死两个痞子?
Then it will be two bitches in the sea.
- 你想这样? - 闭嘴
- Is that what you want? - Shut up.
我老婆知道我不是痞子
My wife know I ain't no bitch.
我是个坏男人
- Yeah. - I'm a bad boy.
坏男人 坏男人 你想干嘛?
Badboys, badboys What you gonna do
他们来找你的时候 你要怎么办?
What you gonna do when they come for you
只有模特儿
Shelly, only models, and that's all.
玛克丝来了 我挂了
Max just dropped by. I have to go.
拜
Bye.
你要我找最近发财的人?
You want me to call around looking for the newly rich?
最近有新面孔花大钱找乐子吗?
Are there any new guys partying a lot, spending a lot of money?
今天有个人打来…
Actually, this guy called me this morning, desperate...
…急著找新鲜小姐
every two hours... looking for new girls in town.
你下午有空吗?
Are you available this afternoon?
- 二千很容易赚 - 我跟茱莉有约
- It will be a quick $2,000. - I've got plans with Julie.
她是你的室友 对吗?
- She's your roommate, right? - Yeah.
叫她来 她很可爱 很性感
Bring her. She's cute. She's sexy. Go on.
- 她不是那种女人,露易丝 - 这个男人吸毒
- She's not a working girl, Lois. - Doesn't matter. He's on speedballs.
吸的太多 根本就硬不起来
He's probably so messed up, he can't even get it up.
好 我们大概可以去看看
Maybe we'll go check it out.
可能是我要找的人
It could be the party I'm looking for.
保尔提默饭店的派对 帅呀
A party at the Bilt more? That will really rock.
算你帮我
- Julie, I owe you one. - Forget about it.
算我还你我欠你的人情
I'll just deduct it from the hundreds off avors I already owe you.
我成了不肯离去的室友?
Am I turning into the guest that won't leave?
不 我喜欢你跟我住
I like having you live with me.
我是个不会煮饭的失业摄影师
I'm an out-of-work photographer who doesn't know how to cook.
省省吧
- Not a big upside for you there. - Come on.
是谁要我们去保尔提默饭店?
What incredibly hip individual inspired this visit to the Bilt more?
帮麦克的忙
- It's a favor for Mike Lowrey. - Right.
对 那个你有点爱的条子
The cop who I think you may be a little bit in love with.
大概吧 我们只是朋友
Maybe I am, but we're just friends.
如果我有麻烦 我只会找他
And if I were ever in trouble, he's the only person I would call.
我知道 你说过了
I know. I think I've heard this before.
你是玛克丝吧
You must be Max.
欢迎 我叫艾迪
Welcome. I'm Eddie.
敬艾尔卡彭套房
The Al Capone suite.
- 我想我们来早了 - 这是茱莉
- I guess we're a little early. - This is my friend, Julie.
你喜欢艾尔卡彭吧?
You like Al Capone, don't you?
我没怎么想过
I hadn't really thought about it much.
我不是在开这儿的玩笑
I'm not kidding about this being Capone's.
他在此装了秘密通道
He had the place rigged with secret passageways.
十分钟后我们就走
Ten minutes, we're out of here.
- 五分钟 - 喝一杯
- Five. - One drink.
- 喝一口
- What's the whispering about? - One sip.
姐妹话
Just girl chat.
厕所在哪?
Where's the bathroom?
楼上右边
Upstairs on your right.
小心走
Watch your step.
过来 坐下
Come. Sit.
好好享受 放松
Enjoy your self. Relax.
艾迪该好好玩玩
Eddie's got some favors to play with.
没错
Yes, Eddie does.
我该早点告诉你
I should have told you sooner about Eddie's private party.
现在是个惊喜派对了
Now it's a surprise party.
玛克丝 我们待够久了
Okay, Max, we've been here about five minutes too long.
你对自己蛮好的 艾迪
I see you treat your self well.
我需要在那任务过后…放松一下
I needed to blow off a little steam after the move, you know?
跟朋友小聚一下
So a little party with a couple of friends. That's all.
本来要邀请你们的
I was gonna invite you guys.
邀请? 我似乎是食物供应者
Invite? It looks like I'm catering this.
我在找两包货 原来在这里
I was looking for my two keys of dope, and now I know where they are.
你的? 是大家的
Yours? It's our score.
- 她是谁? - 无名小卒
- And the girl? - Nobody.
- 来陪我的 - 我是玛克丝
- Just entertainment. - Hi, I'm Max.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我喜欢有自信的女人
I like a woman who takes pride in her appearance.
你呢?
Don't you?
我不喜欢小妞邋邋遢遢的
Yeah, I hate when a bitch lets her self slide.
你穿那衣服像模特儿
You look like a model in that dress.
为我表演好吗?
Will you model for me, Max?
完了 一群大哥
Great. It's the goon squad.
你干过条子 应知妓女大嘴巴
You were a cop for so long, you should know hookers talk.
再四天就交易了 你都等不及?
You couldn't wait four more days until I made the deal?
我无法跟这种白痴合作
I can't work with that kind of stupidity!
我帮你搭的内线
Stupidity? I got you connected inside!
我把弟兄们交给你
I brought you my family.
现在是我的弟兄
Eddie, it's my family now.
我们还是朋友吧
Fouchet, we're still friends.
- 你们干嘛? - 你惹毛他了
- What are you guys doing? - You pissed him off.
又把血喷到我
Use a smaller gun. You got blood on me again.
有人在那上面
- Somebody's upstairs. - Where? Go!
抓她
Get her! Move, Fergie!
Get her!
干他妈的?
What the fuck?
射她
Shoot her!
- 我射中的 - 我射中的
- I got her. Bullshit. - I got her.
- 放屁 我射中的 - 你知道什么是射击?
No, I got her. What do you know about shooting?
不敢相信她逃了
I can't believe she made it.
真的?
- Jesus. - Are you serious?
- 她跳下去了 - 干
- She jumped. - Fuck.
查她在哪上班 住哪里
Find out who she worked for and where she lives.
该是他妈的时候了
It's about fucking time. Lowrey, Burnett, come here!
过来 看到这个人没?
Look at this. You see this guy?
他死了 对吗?
- He's dead, right? - Yeah.
- 眼熟吗? - 艾迪多明哥
- He look familiar? - Eddie Dominguez.
- 以前当过条子 - 你得两分
- The ex-cop. - Two points for you.
我们的高级货在那里
There's some of our high-grade heroin over there.
辛克莱会爱这头条
Sinclair will love that headline.
没有闯入的迹象
There's no signs of forced entry.
这什么? 看起来像贝鲁特战争
What the fuck is all this? It looks like Beirut.
艾尔卡彭套房
It's the Al Capone suite.
我能说什么? 什么事都会发生
What can I say? Shit happens.
末日,真的是末日
This is a real shitty day.
这里有两个唇印
Looks like we have two shades of lipstick here, gentlemen.
有人从派对逃了
Somebody is missing from the party.
听好
Listen to me.
你们现在唯一的方向 就是找到那个人
Your only function in life right now is to find that person. Find her.
那是整天下来唯一的线索
It's the only good lead we got all day.
我去查所有打来这房间的电话
Man, I'll check all calls to the room.
那是什么 兄弟?
What you got over there, partner?
盖上
Cover her.
他认识那女孩?
He knew the girl?
兄弟…
Look, man...
…我们会找到证人和凶手
we'll get the witness and the fools who did this.
看看你能不能 搭豪尔的车回家吧
Yeah. Listen, catch a ride with Howard.
- 你去哪? - 有八通电话打给露易斯菲尔
- Where you going? - Eight calls were made to Lois Fields.
那是玛克丝的老板
That's who Max used to work for. I'll check that out.
- 我跟你去查 - 不 待会见
- I'll come with you. - I'm all right. We'll catch up later.
- 还好吗? - 没事
- You okay? - I'm cool.
哈啰?
Hello?
妈的
Shit.
宝贝 宝贝 我知道品味时光 是我的主意
Yeah, baby. Look, I know quality time was my idea.
- 别谈什么品味时光 - 等等 宝贝
- Don't talk about quality time. - But... Hold on, baby.
给我艾迪多明哥全部资料
Look here, I need a full file on Eddie Dominguez.
需要一会儿
- That will take a minute. - Hold on.
我穿了红色那件
- Marcus, I got on there done. - Baby?
红色那件? 有暗扣那件?
You have on the red one? The one with the snaps?
- 怎不等我? - 你老不在
- Why couldn't you wait till... - You're never home.
资料都冻结了
- Theresa... Hold on. - All his file sareblocked.
我不管他的私人档案
I don't give a damn about his personal files.
- 他已死了 把它解冻 - 干 那是违法的
- The man's dead. Unblock it. - Screw you. That's illegal.
干你
Screw you!
你在跟我说话?
- Fucking... - Marcus, are you talking tome?
不 我不是 那是术语
I'm not talking to... It's a term you use, baby.
- "干你"是警察术语 - 你谁也别想干
- "Screw you" is a cop term. - You ain't screwing nothing!
妈的
Goddamn it!
拉瑞呢?
Where's Lowrey?
我呼叫他了
I just paged him.
他去查露易丝菲尔的线索
He's following up this Lois Fields lead.
那大姐头?
The madam?
请求支援 在瑞奇路614号
21-2, request backup. 614 Reach Road.
教你别搞我们
Don't mess with us.
可能是他
That might be him.
拉瑞办公室
Yeah. Lowrey's desk.
我找麦克拉瑞警官
I need to talk to Detective Mike Lowrey.
我是豪尔探长 有什么事?
This is Captain Howard. Can I help you?
你可以帮我接麦克拉瑞警官?
You can get me Lowrey.
你孩子的爸是他?
This is not another paternity case, is it?
不 这是谋杀案 你这白痴
No, it's another murder case, you twerp.
你是指保尔提默饭店凶案?
Are you talking about the murder case at the Biltmore Hotel tonight?
我看见我好友被杀
Listen, I've just seen my best friend get murdered...
我只要跟拉瑞说
and I'll only talk to Mike Lowrey.
为什么要麦克拉瑞? 我还有
Why only Mike Lowrey? I have a detective here...
干你屁事
None of your fucking business.
我只跟他说 否则我就离城
Either I talk to Lowrey or I'm blowing town.
麦可 电话
Mike, telephone!
他来了 马上来 等等
He's coming right now. Hold on, please.
- 跟她说 - 没时间
- Talk to her. - I ain't got time for these games.
这是那个目击者
This is the witness, the girl at the hotel.
他刚尿尿完 等一下
Yeah, he just got out of the john. Hold on. Talk to her.
- 跟她说 不然她挂了 - 我不是麦克
- If you don't talk to her, she'll walk. - Captain, I can't be Mike.
她要挂了
Just talk to her now. She's gonna walk.
- 她是证人 - 别急
- This is our witness. - Calm down.
哈啰,我是麦克拉瑞
Hello. This is Mike Lowrey.
他不是这样说话的 学他说话
He doesn't talk that way. Try to talk sexy.
声音性感点 你的声音不够性感
- Come on. - You don't sound sexy enough.
妈的
Captain! I've been there.
你不认识我 我叫茱莉摩特
You don't know me. My name's Julie Mott.
我是玛克丝的挚友
I was Max Logan's best friend.
冷静点.跟我说吧
Whoa. Calm down. Talk to me now.
她说若她需要帮助…
- Yeah. - She said if she ever needed anything...
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
地址给我.好
Give me the address. All right.
没事了 麦克来救你
It's gonna be all right. Mike's to the rescue.
- 我马上到 - 我试试看能不能找到拉瑞
- I'm on the way. All right. - I'll see if I can find Lowrey.
- 我不能去 - 你得去
- I can't go. - You have to go.
- 去 - 叫麦克来处理
- Go! - Get Mike down here to handle this.
马上去这个地址 起来
Get to this address now. Get out of the chair.
否则一个月不准回家 起来
- You won't see your wife for a month! - Goddamn it, man.
把这他妈的门修好
Get this fucking door fixed.
轻轻地 麦克拉瑞
Easy.
妈的
Shit.
- 是谁? - 麦克拉瑞
- Who's there? - Mike Lowrey.
我怎么知道你是麦克拉瑞?
How do I know it's Mike Lowrey?
因为我就是麦克拉瑞
'Cause I'm Mike Lowrey.
时间不多了
We ain't got much time.
把警徽放在监视孔
Hold your badge up to the peephole.
否则不让你进来
I'm not letting you in until you do!
想得美
No way.
- 你干嘛? - 你不是他
- What was that for? - You're not Mike Lowrey!
什么意思? 你从没见过他
What do you mean? You never even met him... me.
- 你不像玛克丝形容的 - 我在卧底
- Max described you differently! - I'm undercover!
证明一下
- All right! - Prove it!
我认识玛克丝很久了
I knew Max from way back.
- 我帮玛克丝弟弟减刑 - 然后呢?
- I helped her brother get out of jail. - Yeah, so?
我就是这么酷 我们…常常窃窃私语
So, from time to time, we'd get together, a little bump and grind.
错 棒子给我
- Wrong. - Give me that!
你需要脱困却不信我? 算了
Give me the bat! You want to go out? Fine!
好 你自己玩吧
You don't want to believe me, you go at this shit alone!
我忘了 坏蛋知道 你住哪里…
I forgot! The bad guys probably know where you live.
…而且他们正在找你 祝好运
Which means they're coming for your ass. Good luck.
我全都看见
I saw the whole thing.
看见他杀她像杀只狗一样
I watched them shoot her like she was nothing.
请关门
Please shut the door.
小姐
Look, lady...
你不会再拿球棒 高尔夫球杆…
do you have any more bats, golf clubs...
…或别的东西打我了吧?
or anything like that you could swing at me?
我认识玛克丝 知道吗?
I knew Max.
我也关心她
I care about Max also.
我是来帮你的
I'm just here to help you.
我不知道你长这样
You're not what I expected.
我不期望我可以进洋基运动场
I didn't expect to walk into Yankee Stadium either.
我们得离开 知道吗? 走吧
Now, we have to get out of here. Let's go.
我得带小狗 来 公爵
I have to get my dogs. Come here, Dukie.
公爵 母爵 随便啦
Come here, Lukie, Dukie, whatever.
有后门吗?
You got a back door?
去哪里?
Where are we going?
- 保护看管所 - 去他的 我只跟著你
- Protective custody. - Fuck that. I'm only dealing with you.
饭店开派对的是条子
That was a cop that threw that little party back at the Biltmore.
以前是条子 我们让他滚蛋很久了
Former cop. We got rid of him a long time ago.
- 来 母爵 - 听好
- Come on, Luke. - Listen, lady.
想活命就得相信我
If you want to live, you ain't got no choice. You got to trust me.
来 小狗 狗狗来
- Get the dog! - Here, doggie!
天呀 那是谁?
Jesus Christ! Who the hell was that?
杀太多人了 傅革森会很不高兴的
- Let's go! - There is too much killing going on!
- 去追他们 - 我去前面
- Go after them! I'll go around front! - I got them!
快跑 我们快走
Come on! Move your ass! Let's go!
干
Fuck.
快上车
- Get in the car! - Damn it.
- 上车 - 烂门
- Go, goddamn it! - Fucking door!
你让人跑了? 肥猪头
How did you miss them? You fat fuck!
嘴巴干净点
Watch your fucking mouth!
减肥就可逮住人
If you'd lose some weight, you would have caught them!
我想扭掉你烂头
I'd like to squeeze your little fucking head, you bastard!
你麻烦大了
Now you're in fucking trouble!
- 看到牌照没? - 看了
- You get the license plate? - Yeah, I got the fucking plate.
烂头
You cockeyed fuck.
这叫逃亡车? 这怎么逃
This is your getaway car?
这是全家福车吗?
We won't get away from anything in this. Is this a goddamn family station wagon?
天啊 你后座还有婴儿座
My God, you have a baby seat in the back.
这是伪装车 知道吗? 伪装车
It's an undercover car.
妈的 他们看到我的牌照了
Shit! I know they got a look at my license plate.
是他们杀的吗?
Were those the guys who shot Max?
我只看见子弹
What guys? I only saw bullets.
你告诉我他们长相怎样
You tell me what they looked like.
我忙著保护你
I don't know! I was too busy trying to keep a bullet out your ass!
我需要你要去看档案…
Julie, I'll need you to look through some mug shots...
…指认凶手
until you can identify Max's shooter.
- 哪里? - 保护看管所
- Where will we do that? - Protective custody.
不 我说了我不去
No way! I told you I am not going into protective custody!
别闹了 你惹毛我了
Look, lady, I'm not playing. You're really pissing me off!
我就逮捕你
I'll book your narrow ass!
我突然得了健忘症了
Yeah? I'll develop amnesia.
脑袋一片空白
I suddenly feel a little case of it coming on right now.
好 你觉得哪安全?
Fine, lady. Where would you feel safe?
你想要保护我?
You want to do protective custody?
在你家保护
We'll do in-home protective custody.
我可以接受
At your place, all right? I can handle going to your place.
我家
Yeah, my place.
我家很不行
My place is... No way.
对 我家很可怕
Right. My place. Yeah, my place is shit.
你对 麦克家
Mike Lowrey place. You right.
这是你今晚最好的主意
That's the best idea you came up with tonight.
考琳斯公园
在这等
Wait here.
伯纳警官
- Detective Burnett, how are you ? - I'm cool.
- 你好? 很久不见了 拉瑞先生不在 - 我知道
- Mr. Lowrey's not here. He's out. - I know.
他说我可以来
- He said I could use his place tonight. - Really?
他没跟我说
He didn't mention it to me.
小妞是谁? 老婆好吗?
Who's the chick? How's your wife?
很好 她很好
She's fine.
孩子好吧?
Your kids are good?
- 家最重要 - 是吗?
- Family's the most important thing. - Is it?
拉瑞先生说你家是生孩子工厂
Mr. Lowrey told me you got a baby factory going on at your house.
拿去
- Is that true? - Here you go.
如果嫌少就以敲诈罪逮捕你
If that ain't enough, I'll run you in for extortion.
有时候我很笨
You know, I'm so stupid sometimes.
- 是吗? - 好在你提醒我
- Are you ? - Now that you mention it...
拉瑞先生说过你会来
Mr. Lowrey did mention you coming by tonight.
他说什么? 他有说起钥匙吗?
What did he say? Did he say he had a key?
等等 - 拿去
- Hang out. Here you go. - Hang out?
- 就是这个? - 你弄痛我了
- Is this it? - Yeah. You're hurting me.
- 谢了 - 很高兴见到你
- Thank you . - Good to see you.
- 很高兴见到你 - 好好玩
- Good to see you . - Have fun.
不是那样,我不是那种人
- It's not like that. - Sure.
来 小心走
Yeah, come on. Watch your step walking through.
我大概放了芳香剂
Damn, I must have left some incense burning.
欢迎到拉瑞王国
Welcome to Casa de Lowrey.
这有点…
This is kind of...
我老是换开关的位置
I'm always moving my switches.
我常常装潢 连开关都找不到
I'm always decorating, so sometimes I just don't know where shit is.
妈的
Damn! Shit!
我为什么会在 熟悉的地方被绊到?
Why am I tripping on shit I know is there?
你找到开关了
You found a light switch.
是我装潢的 我应该记得在哪里
I should have known it was there since I decorated the place.
这是伊薇
Hi, Mike. This is Yvette.
伊薇 她是我恶梦
Ignore this. It's one of my freaks, Yvette.
老打来 太饥渴了
She's always calling. Got to have it.
别打了 怪人
Don't call no more now, freak.
条子薪水付得起吗?
- All this on a cop's salary? - I feel like having your right now...
这是干净钱
It's honest money.
我是第二代富家子
I'm a second generation rich kid.
如果你不是因为薪水袋
So if you're not in it for the paycheck...
那你大概是武打烂人吧?
are you some kind of action junkie?
可以那么说
Yeah. If that's what you want to call it.
我不怕球棒打 子弹飞
I don't mind bats swung at my head, bullets damn near grazing my ass.
我爱这些刺激 听着…
Gives me a rush. Look...
…我告诉你这里的情况
let me give you a broad stroke of the place.
冰箱有牛排给小狗吃…
Got some T-bones in the fridge for Luke and Dukie.
对不起 你的冰箱在这边
Sorry. Your fridge is this way.
- 我脑子昏了 - 等一下
- I confuse my own shit. - Wait a minute.
- 你要把我留在这? - 我得回警局
- You're leaving me here alone? - Yeah, I have to get back to work.
- 迈阿密有太多的犯罪案 - 显然是
- These are Miami's peak crime hours. - Apparently.
他们说这买卖 四天内就敲定…
They said that this deal was going down in four days.
…他们一定有些漏洞
I obviously seem to be kind of a major glitch...
你现在不跟坏人在一起
You ain't with the bad guys now.
你现在跟警察在一起了
You're with the cops...
跟麦克在一起 你现在跟警察在一起了
with Mike Lowrey.
一切都没事了 相信我
Everything will be all right. Trust me.
我会回来
I'll be back.
我知道这不是开玩笑的时候 但记不记得在电影里…?
I know there's no time to joke, but remember in the movie...
好了
All right.
谢谢你 麦克
Thanks for everything, Mike.
我走了
I'm going.
你动作真快
- Chet. - That was quick. You one of those guys?
不是那种事 那个女孩
- In and out. - It's not like that.
她是证人,看好她
The girl's a witness. I need you to keep an eye out.
- 没问题 - 仔细听好
- No problem. - Now listen to me.
- 我? - 没错
- Hear me. That's right. - Me?
拉瑞一但来了 就叫他打到我家
The moment Lowrey gets in, have him call me at home.
- 打到我家 - 打到你家
- At my home. - Call you at home.
别让他上去
Use this phone. Do not let him go upstairs.
别让他上去? 但他住这里
Don't let him go upstairs? But he lives here.
我会被炒鱿鱼的
I don't want to argue with Mr. Lowrey. I could lose my job.
查特 相信我好吗?
Trust me on this, okay?
从这里打给你 别让他上去
Call you from here. Don't let him up.
- 没问题 - 重要证人
- No problem. - Important witness.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道了 我两小时后下班…
I got a better idea. I'm getting off in two hours.
…可以上楼去守门
If you want, I could go upstairs and watch the door.
像电影里面的条子一样
Like the cops do in the movies? They sit on a stool?
我有杂志看
I got a magazine and everything.
不让任何人进出
I don't let anybody in or out.
真的 我想帮你忙
Seriously, all kidding aside, I want to help.
从这里帮行吗?
You're helping. Can you do it from here?
- 可以 - 那就好
- Yeah, I can do it from here. - Fine.
从这里帮 好吗?
- That helps. From here, okay? - All right.
你让我想起我本来可当条子
It's funny that you ask me, because I was going to be a cop.
我去考试了
I took the test.
但没成功.政策问题
Just didn't work out. Politics.
你是我代理人
- You're my deputy. - I'm your deputy.
- 是 - 待在这里 注意了 - 好
- Watch out for everything. - You got it.
保重
Take care, Chief.
我是代理人
I'm a deputy.
别说好话 你闻起来像香水
Don't "honey baby" me. You smell like perfume.
婚戒也没戴
You don't even have your wedding ring on!
妈的
Damn.
我伪装出勤…
I went undercover.
…那不准戴婚戒
It required taking off the ring for a second, but I got the ring.
但我把戒指放在口袋里…
I just put my hand in my pocket because that's where it was...
…已经戴好了
and it's right back on, baby.
枕头给我好吗?
Can I get a pillow?
这不是不回电的那人吗
If it isn't the guy who doesn't return phone calls.
这12个小时你都在哪?
Where have you been the last 12 hours?
我呼叫你整晚
I've been paging you all night.
有些你必须知道的情况
We got a situation here you need to know about.
马可士…
Look, I got a dead madam...
…我有个死了的大姐头 一个脑震荡还有头痛得很
I got a concussion and I got a real bad headache.
我告诉你我昨晚做了什么吧
You got a headache? Let me tell you what I did last night.
我昨晚睡沙发
I had to sleep on my couch.
醒来后屁股上还有机器战警
I wake up with a Power Ranger stuck up my ass.
而且屁股差点被轰掉了
And while we're discussing my ass, I damn near got it blown off.
好消息是我找到证人
But the good news is I got a witness.
我告诉你这证人… 她想
Let me tell you about this witness. She likes to...
- 你跟个阿婆一样唠叨 - 我唠叨…? 我唠叨?
- You sound like a nagging wife. - I'm nagging.
你没我就怎样了? 就出事了
You see what happens when you go off with out me? You get into shit.
好像你在就不会出事
Like shit don't happen when you're there.
不是说这个
That ain't the point.
我是说如果你的搭档呼叫你
The point is if your partner pages you ...
你也许想回个电
you might want to get back to your partner.
我要看是谁惹你
I want to meet the man who whupped your ass.
我想看看是谁惹我兄弟 那就是我想做的
I want to meet who whupped Shaft's ass.
看看我 你不知道 我昨晚受了什么罪
Look at me, man. You don't know what I've been through.
我老婆把我扫地出门了 把我扫出温馨的家门了
My wife kicked me out of the house, kicked me out of my happy home.
而你自己找乐子去了 还只会说"我来处理"这套
But you got to go off by your self. "I got this, partner."
去你的
Bullshit.
我好多了 谢了
I am feeling much better, though, thank you.
我会逮到他
- Yeah. - And I'll get his ass.
他把你打成这样 你小心点
Be cool. Watch your self.
我说什么? 听见我说的没?
What did I say? Did you hear what I said?
我听见了 因为 我说的时候我在那里
I heard what I said 'cause I was standing there when I said it.
我叫你去保护证人…
I told you to secure a witness.
…不是扫射住宅区
Not to shoot up a neighborhood! Not to do another dead body!
不要有别的死人了 赶快安安静静的把毒品找回来
Just get the dope back, and do it quietly.
情况有些难以控制
Look, Captain, this whole situation is getting out of control.
说得好 情况确实有些难以控制
- You're goddamn right! - Look, man...
她先考验我 才相信我是他
I damn near had to pass a pop quiz before she believed I was him.
进 进…妈的 差一点
Going, going... Shit. A little off.
我今天没杀人
I haven't killed anybody yet today, Captain.
你要我吼你吗?
Do you want me to yell at you ? I can do that.
让我告诉你 这证人是唯一可喜的消息
Let me tell you something. This witness is my only good news.
你们只会带来厄运 什么意思?
You guys are bad news. So what does that mean?
不管你是麦可拉瑞还是圣诞老人
If you have to be Mike Lowrey, Santa Claus, FD Hutton...
我都不理 就是这样
that's what you're gonna be!
等等 怎么回事?
Wait a minute. What the hell is going on here?
你们来了之后我全都没投进
I was getting them all in before you showed up.
谁告诉我怎么回事行吗?
Can somebody talk to me, please? Can I know what's going on?
那些人很可能看到我牌照了
Captain, these fools could have got a look at my license plate last night.
她人呢?
Where's the girl now?
- 他家 - 什么?
- His place. - What?
你丢下她一个人? 唯一的证人?
You left her by herself? Our only fucking witness?
你把妓女放在我家?
You left a strange hooker alone in my apartment?
据我所知 她不是妓女
The girl is not a hooker, as far as I know.
我得安置她们 她和狗儿
I had to stash her somewhere; her and her dogs, Luke and Dukie.
你把狗放我家?
So you left dogs in my house?
有狗和妓女在我家?
There's dogs and a hooker in my house?
加只猩猩 我们就可以开嘉年华会了
How about you add some chimps? We can have a carnival.
她不是妓女
I said she isn't a hooker.
- 拜托你? - 闭嘴
- Can you please... - Shut up!
多年来 辛克莱一直找我碴
For years, Sinclair has been up my ass, trying to pin something on me.
我都帮你们扛了 帮我个忙
I'm always taking it for you . Do it for me!
这证人若能指认凶手
If we get this witness to identify the shooters...
也许能逮到坏蛋
maybe we catch our bad guys.
但逮到人之前…在那之前, 你还是麦可拉瑞
But until then, you are Mike Lowrey.
你是他 你就是他
You be him. That's what you are. You're him.
你是他 不准再吵
I don't want to hear it. And you ...
你是你 你在她面前不是你
You're you . You be you , but not in front of her.
你是他 你是你
You're him! You're you!
等一下好吗? 我算什么? 被设计的流浪汉?
Can we get a time-out, Captain? Am I the designated homeless?
我会在乎吗?
Does it look like I care?
全力以赴 可以吗?
Whatever it takes, all right?
她跟你说什么? 四天内买卖就会完成
What did she say to you ? The shooters are making their drop in four days?
我们有四天的时间
So we got four days.
这什么计划?
Captain, what kind of plan is that?
我不能跟她住
I can't be shacked up with that woman.
我有家庭要照顾 我老婆会宰了我
I have a family to look after. My wife will kill my ass!
不想干? 辞职呀
You don't like your job? Quit.
妈的
Damn!
我去陪泰莉莎和孩子
Look, I'll stay at the house with Theresa and the kids.
谢了 不必
Thank you , but no thanks.
你撑不了五分钟
You wouldn't last five minutes with my family.
少来了 婚姻生活很简单 只要满足一个女人
Please, married life is easy. You only got one woman to satisfy.
兄弟…别说笑了
Yo, man. We ain't the Cosbys.
走吧 我来投
Let's go. I got this.
走吧
Go.
大家都想当麦克
Every body wants to be like Mike.
对 你也可以像他一样退休
Yeah, and you're gonna be retired like him too.
我会打你的屁股
I'd have dunked it on your ass.
克里弗兰? 我从没有…
Cleveland? I have never...
听著 我跟你说过了…
Look, woman, I done told you.
…是政府要我去作证
It's a federal subpoena.
我能说不吗?
Am I supposed to tell them no?
我不知道 为何不派他?
I don't know what you'll tell them. Why can't he go?
- 为何不派你? - 我也想
- Why can't you go? - I wanted to...
但豪组长说我不负
but Captain Howard said I'm irresponsible.
不 他说我太暴力 会乱开枪
No, he said, "A loose cannon," because I've been shooting in public.
- 常常失控 - 够了
- Out of now here sometimes. - Mike, please.
宝贝 附近小偷很多
Look, baby, the neighborhood has had a lot of break-ins.
我会留意 我不需要麦克
I can handle it. I don't need Mike to handle it.
我操心我自己
I know you can handle it, but I'm worrying about me.
麦克留下照应你还有孩子们
Mike's going to stay here with you and the kids, take care of y'all...
直到我回来
just till I come back.
谁去幼儿所接孩子?
Who will pick the kids up from day care and all that?
- 麦克不会 - 听到我说的吗 宝贝? 我说
- Mike can't do it. - Are you listening to me? I said...
有本书能帮你们忙
I read a book that could probably help y'all. I saw it on...
你去喝可乐好吗?
Mike, can you go down and have a Coke and a smile?
- 拜托 - 好吧
- Please? - All right.
你要点什么?
Y'all want something?
给我可乐
Bring me a Coke.
- 你要吗? - 不了 谢了
- Baby, you want a Coke? - I'm fine, thank you.
好啦
All right.
解释一下?
Explain it to me, Elliot.
化学器具有问题吗?
We've got a problem with our chemistry set?
不是化学器具的问题
It's not a chemistry set.
他知道不是化学器具的问题
He knows it ain't a chemistry set, asshole.
那么 是什么问题?
What is it?
混合体是非常不稳定的…物质
The cutting agent is a highlyvolatile substance.
- 乙醚 - 我不管
- The ether... - I don't care.
我不是化学老师 白痴
I'm not a fucking chemistry teacher.
- 是什么问题? - 这里太潮湿了
- What is the problem? - There's too much moisture here.
- 对 根本没法干活 - 闭嘴
- Yeah, it's totally fucked. - You shut up!
还有呢?
What else?
分解的时间比我们 计划的还要久…
It's taking longer to cook than we originally planned.
…如果太急就做不成了
If we rush it, we'll have a lot of drugs we can't sell.
你在乱搞我的时间表 我给过你截止期
You're fucking with my timetable. I gave you a deadline.
- 懂吗? - 懂了
- Do you understand? - Yeah, I understand.
- 有穿衣服吧? - 有
- You dressed? - Yeah. I am.
我们要查看档案
Look, we have to go through some mug shots.
我接了电脑,我们做的到的
I'll hook into the computer. We can do this.
照片上的人是谁?
Mike, who's the guy in all the photographs?
太少看书架
Sometimes I don't even look at my shelves.
都忘了那摆了照片
I forget all the pictures were here.
是我搭档 叫马可士伯纳
That's my partner, Marcus Burnett.
我从没碰过这事
I've never seen anything like this before.
我了解你为何吃惊
I can see how it may throw you a little bit.
是警察的默契
It's a cop thing.
他救我一命 我就 摆他一张照片
These pictures are up here for every time he saved my life.
他的家也一样 都是我的照片
If you go to his place ain't nothing but pictures of me.
像是个神坛 有纪念意义的
It's like a shrine. Just a reminder.
我看墙上全是…
Because when I saw it, and it was the whole wall...
…以为是你…爱人的照片
I thought maybe they were pictures of your lover.
- 谁? - 以为你是同性恋
- Of who? - I thought maybe you were gay.
我是同性恋? 不 不是
That I was gay? No, baby.
我无意冒犯 同性恋没什么嘛
I didn't mean to offend you. It's okay to be a homosexual.
你没听懂 你没仔细听 对吗?
You're not listening. It's not registering.
相信我 你有睡床吗?
Believe me. Did you sleep in the bed?
你没感到凹陷吗? 做爱的凹陷
Didn't you feel the dents? The dents come from all that.
我跟女人做爱
That's how I get down.
那…很好
That's sweet.
我是同性恋
Gay.
如果我是 房里窗帘就得换
If I was, I'd change the drapes in this motherfucker.
- 来一点? - 不 谢了 我不吃血淋淋的肉
- Want some? - No, thanks. I don't eat flesh.
什么?
What?
你嘴里…嚼的是血淋淋的肉
That's flesh that you're shoveling into your mouth.
曾是活的生物
That was a living, breathing creature.
甚至有过名字
It probably had a name.
这只是香肠
It's just baloney.
我的香肠有名字
My baloney has a first name.
事实上 你香肠有30个名字…
Actually, your baloney has about 30 names...
…它们取自不同生物的 奇怪部位
because they take odd parts from all different ones...
剩余的内脏 胃壁 耳朵…
Like the leftovers: The hooves and stomach lining...
…之类的 他们把那个放进…
ears, stuff like that.
…一种机器绞碎
They put it into this machine and grind it all up.
你嘴里吃的
Then out comes this sheet.
就是这玩意
That's what you're eating now.
你知道吗? 我不吃香肠了
You know what? I won't eat baloney no more.
腌黄瓜如何? 能吃腌黄瓜吗?
How about a pickle? Can I eat it?
是盐腌的 但是蔬菜
It has a lot of salt, but it's fine. It is a vegetable.
腌黄瓜有盐? 我洗洗
A lot of salt in the pickle? Let me rinse it off.
可以了 可以了
There we go.
这样如何?
How's that?
- 继续看照片吧 - 我连盐的味道都尝不到
- Just keep going. - I don't even taste the salt now.
跳回去
Go back.
是他
That's the guy.
他在那房里
He was there in the room.
情报得知他们有50公斤毒品
We got a tip they were running major drugs, something like 50 keys.
我们走向门去
So we step to the door. Boom!
"别动 警察 趴下 趴下 趴下 "
Freeze! Miami Police Department! Get down!
一个不知道从哪来叫奇诺的人 打了我头
Out of now here, this little crazy pimp named Chino punched me in the head.
奇诺是三七 你爸会解释
Chino had been running whores. Your dad will explain that to you.
看看这个 你的狗在我屋里大便
Look at it. Your dogs are shitting all over my place.
拉稀的
Liquid shit.
拿家俱漆来盖是没用的?
It doesn't help when you shell ack it in with furniture polish.
那边有一块 快擦
There's a piece right there. Please, get that.
- 我擦 - 看起来像狗屎块
- Fine. - It looks like a chip of shit.
诺不查菲肯的资料给我好吗?
Can I please have the parole jacket on Noah Trafficante?
- 谢谢 - 你知道吗?
- Thank you . - You know what?
那证人把我烦死了
I'm getting tired of this witness.
我要过原来日子
I want to get back to my life the way it was.
我好累 我结婚了 我不用再骗人
I'm tired. I got married so I could stop lying.
我不相信你在抱怨
I cannot believe you're complaining.
你比我好多了 我住在你叫家的动物园里
You got it easy compared to me, living in that zoo you call home.
你为什么叫我家动物园?
Why you have to call my place a zoo?
- 我受够你了 - 想打架?
- I'm tired of you saying that. - You want to fight me.
听著 法兰欣 请…
- Don't call my place a zoo. - Listen... Francine, please...
- 那是我的丝衬衫 - 这不错
- That's my silk shirt, man! - Yeah, it is kind of nice.
既然要当麦克 就得像他
Since I'm gonna be like Mike, I might as well dress like Mike.
我想要 我想当麦克
I wanna be like Mike
你真恶心 你有毛病
You're sick. Something is wrong with you.
你该去检查脑袋
You have a problem, and you should have your self checked.
可能
Yeah. Probably.
这是档案 他在地狱酒店上班
- Here's the file. He works at Club Hell. - Thank you.
这个给你处理吧?
Take care of this, please.
- 我要打给老婆 - 谁的?
- I've got to call the wife. - Whose wife?
你干点正事行吗?
Can you please do some work?
今天就帮点忙吧
One time today, just do something.
- 帮点忙查案子 - 老天
- Do something that helps this case. - Boy...
你今天看起来很帅
You look real handsome today.
别跟我闹
See, it's not that kind of day.
少烦我
Leave me the fuck alone.
我是真的
Seriously. All right?
- 什么事 宝贝? 月事来啦? - 烂笑话
- What's up? PMS? - Damn the jokes.
妈的 滚 别惹我
Ring it. I ain't in the mood.
好呀 等等
Yeah, that's cool. Hold on.
写下来
All right. Write it down.
好
All right.
孩子好吗?
- How are things going with the kids? - They're fine. You okay?
上厕所教得如何?
- How's potty training going? - Slowly but surely.
- 你真傻 - 会晚回吗?
- You are so silly. - Are you going to be late tonight?
不 大约十点半或十一点回去
It will be 10:30, 11:00 before I get in.
别等我 我会回来
- Later. - Don't wait up. I'll be all right.
租个带子 看点轻松的
Why don't you rent a movie? Something we can kick back to.
- 你穿什么? - 电话给我 给我
- What you wearing? - Give me the phone!
她早就挂了 我闹你的
- Baby! - She hung up a long time ago.
我闹你的
I was playing.
别闹 你在分裂
Hey, man, don't play like that.
一个快乐的家庭
That's my family. Don't break up a happy home.
你别再穿我的衣服了
Stop wearing my clothes then.
今天大家都想开我玩笑
Everybody's about the jokes today, ain't they? Hello?
我不信
I cannot believe this.
艾迪的档案不会那么难进
This Eddie Dominguez file cannot be that hard to get into.
我试了三次都进不去
I've tried three times. I just can't get in.
而且这违法
Besides, this is illegal.
你以前都可以
Yeah, that never stopped you before.
有消息通知我
Just let me know if you get anything.
我会为你做任何事 但我实在进不去
Anything for you , but I can't get in. I tried.
- 你好吗 查特? - 拉瑞先生
What's up, Chet?
拉瑞兄弟团
The Lowrey Brothers.
去地狱酒店抓诺尔吧
Let's just get down to Club Hell and pick up Noah.
茱莉 是我
Julie, it's me.
你应该给我多明哥的资料
You're supposed to be getting us into this Eddie Dominguez file.
要一两天
It's gonna be a day or two before I can get Fletch out.
- 没时间了 - 我不是电脑神通
- We don't have a day or two. - I'm not the computerwhiz.
需要时间
It's gonna take a while before we can hack the computer.
- 你什么也办不好 - 我在想
- You're not taking care of shit. - Mike, I was thinking about something...
- 嗨 你一定是马可士 - 我是
- You must be Marcus. - I'm Marcus.
- 没错 - 是马可士吧?
- That's right. - Right.
我是茱莉
I'm Julie.
茱莉 你好 很高兴见你
Julie. All right. It's nice to meet you.
你也是 我是从所有的照片上认出你的
You too. I recognize you from every one of the photographs.
他是我哥们
Yeah. He's my man, so we...
墙上所有的照片
All those on the wall.
你一定很行
- Yeah. - You must be very good.
什么?
I'm sorry?
在你的工作上很行
As a partner. Your job, what you do.
今晚几点去干?
What time are we doing this thing tonight?
- 什么? - 麦克说我们要去酒店
- Excuse me? - Mike said we were going to a club.
"我们"…是指我和我兄弟
Yeah. "We" as in me and my partner.
你要住家保护看管 你留在家里
You wanted home protective custody. You're at my house.
太好了
That's just great.
我留在这里
So I'll just stay here again...
让查特那白痴保护?
with Chet the mini-moron doorman to protect me?
查特很行的
Chet is very good.
你地毯上好像有污点 该死
I'm sorry. That looks like a stain on your rug.
是我狗狗公爵
- Damn. - That was my baby, Luke.
他一到新地方就紧张
He gets kind of nervous in new surroundings.
然后就会拉屎
- He just shits, huh? - Yeah.
就像雄性动物在领域作记号
It's like marking his territory. It's sort of a male thing.
我要付清洗钱 但他不要
I offered to pay Mike for the cleaning, and he wouldn't hear of it.
- 我反正要丢了 - 你不需要那个
- I'm getting rid of it. - Yeah, you don't need that.
我反正要把那丢出去 我要换新的了
I'm throwing that out anyway. I just want a new look.
麦克是很特别的人 很特别的人
Mike is a special guy. Boy, Mike is special.
我叫他怪人麦克
I call him "Special Mike."
这真的很有趣 所以…
It's funny how you can just laugh at that.
…我这么爱他
That's why I love him. Now, me?
换作我 我会气炸
I'd be pissed.
- 沙发上有只好可爱的狗 - 那是母爵
- Look at this cute dog on the couch. - That's Luke.
- 看他把沙发抓成这样 - 你要看公爵吗? 它在床上
- Look how he crawls on the leather. - You want to meet Duke? He's in bed.
它不舒服…
He's been feeling upset and having diarrhea...
…又拉又吐一早上
and throwing up all morning.
宝贝
Oh, baby.
去看看公爵好点没?
Let's go see if little Duke is gonna be okay, shall we?
我跟你 我跟你
Me and you.
- 你是谁? - 你是谁?
- Lady, who are you ? - Who the hell are you?
- 你得出去 - 别碰我
- You have to get out. - Get your hands off me!
- 别推我 - 我是伊薇
- Lady, don't push me! - I'm Yvette.
- 把手拿开 - 你干嘛?
- You're not any Yvette I know. - What are you doing?
快走
Get out of here, all right?
再跟踪我就逮捕你 老变态
If you don't stop stalking me, I'll arrest your ass, you old psycho!
- 你这王八 - 她有点不对劲
- You asshole! - Woman's into some weird shit.
怎么回事?
- What is going on out here? - Excuse me.
那个疯伊薇
That was crazy Yvette...
跟踪我
stalking me.
我忘了她要来 你把伊薇弄走了?
Yvette? I forgot she was coming. You threw her out?
伊薇是按摩师
Yvette is a masseuse.
功夫好极了
She massages shit.
她说过了
- She told me. - Listen...
今晚还有哪个…
are there any other totally hysterical...
…半裸的疯女会来这里?
half-naked women popping by tonight that I should know about?
- 她没穿衣服 - 一丝不挂
- She was naked? - Titties were out a little bit.
你让她一丝不挂就出去?
You threw Yvette out naked?
我老婆恨 她最恨玩女人的男人了
You're something... My wife would hate... She hates womanizers.
你这样不对
- There's something wrong with you . - There is?
你不尊重人 跟你说了多少年了
You don't respect other people's shit. I've told you that for years.
你的垃圾到处都是
Ever since we started, you always have your trash all over.
够了 拜托
Enough! Please!
我跟我的搭档…
Me and my partner...
…我们要去酒店抓诺尔
are going to Club Hell to bust this fool Noah.
谁有意见?
Does anybody have a problem with that?
好
Fine.
别搞砸了
Don't blow the case.
地狱酒店
这样吧 你留著 任何人叫你离开 千万不要
Frank, here's the deal: You stay put. Anybody tells you to move, don't.
你就说帮傅谢送东西 听懂没? 法兰克
Tell them you're making a delivery for Mr. Fouchet. You got it?
这是乙醚 会爆的
Jeez. It's ether! It will explode!
白痴
You dope!
最好别呼吸 笨蛋
Don't even breathe, you knucklehead!
诺尔…我记得你
I remember you.
你看 拉瑞…只剩两天 别搞砸了
Check it. We got two days left. Let's try to do this right.
别开枪 别杀人
No gunshots, no dead bodies.
我不想丢工作
I'm not trying to lose my job on this one.
我记得上次杀人的是你
If I recall correctly, the last couple dead bad guys belonged to you.
下次杀人前…
And next time you have to kill them...
…先问出我们要的资料
do it after you get the information we need.
只是个建议
That's just a suggestion.
拜托 别比谁毙的人多
Please. You ain't even trying to compare body counts.
还要数吗? 不够数了
One... Should I keep going? Damn, I'm out.
档案上说他在此工作
This guy Noah's parole jacket says he works in there.
我们在这里像小女孩在吵架
We're standing out front arguing like a couple of school girls.
别再说废话了
Why don't we put an end to all this bickering?
你快惹毛我了
- All right. - ' Cause you're getting on my nerves.
- 看看你 看看你 专心点行吗? - 我很专心
- Look at you . Can you stay focused? - What? I'm focused!
专心看小姐
Yeah, focused on all this scattered ass here.
让我们把事情办了走人
Let's do what we came to do and get out of here.
- 简单 - 好
- Simple. - Fine. Let's split up, check around.
- 查查看 10分钟吧台见 - 好
- Meet me at the bar in ten minutes. - Fine.
妈的 他来这里干嘛?
Holy shit. What the hell is he doing? Man!
是那个条子 他在那 看见没?
That's the cop! There he is! See him?
是他 我去
- That's him! - Yeah, I'm going!
怎么了?
What's up?
灌太多啤酒了
Budweiser. Feel like I had a million of them.
怎样?
What's up, motherfucker?
告诉我那女孩在哪里
Tell me where the dough is, jack-off!
干
Fuck!
下次用屁股去学怎么用安全栓
Next time learn how to work the safety with your punk ass!
我会回来
I'll be back.
- 谁扁你了? - 不是说笑的时候
- Who whupped your ass now? - This really ain't the fucking time.
他们知道了 快抓诺尔走人
They know. Let's get Noah and get out of here.
是那小妞
The chick!
看 那小妞 在屋顶上的女人
The girl! The bitch from the rooftop!
- 走 - 是他杀玛克丝的
- Let's go! - That was the guy who shot Max!
卡车 上卡车
The truck! Let's take the truck!
快 走
Right there!
我们赶时间
Move! We're really in a hurry.
- 快走 - 你们是条子 我们干嘛要跑?
- Let's go! - You're cops! Why are we running away?
- 他在那里面 - 快 开车
- He's in there! - Here! Go!
太好了, 诺尔在追我们
This is good. Noah's chasing us!
你想怎样?
What was that?
想…我不知道
- That was- - I don' t know.
我有绝佳的机会可打中他 如果武打王杰克森
But I had a good shot at him if your friend Action Jackson over here...
不 这是警方的事
This is official police business!
不干你的事
You had no business in there!
快点开车好吗?
And can you please drive this thing?
- 快开 - 别催我好吗?
Don't bring it here, all right?
是你选这冰淇淋车的
You picked this slow-ass ice cream truck!
- 什么味道? - 快开
- What am I smelling? - Just drive!
乙醚 极易燃烧的乙醚
Ether. Extremely flammable ether.
- 妈的 - 妈的
- Shit. - Goddamn.
都是你 都是你害的
You the man! You the fucking man tonight!
你怎么选个是 炸弹的冰淇淋车?
You pick an ice cream truck that's a damn bomb!
妈的
Shit!
- 这叫保护看管? - 没错
- This is protective custody? - Yes!
想想办法 快没路了
You better do something, boy! We're running out of road!
谁选的路?
Who picked this road?
迈阿密有这么多路 都会被你走到没路走
All the road in Miami, and you're running out of it!
- 快想办法 - 干嘛要我想?
- You better get an idea fast! - Why are the ideas always up to me?
- 交给你了 - 路到底了 没路了
- Take this shit! - It's a dead end! There's no more road!
没路可开了
We're out of fucking road!
- 那会爆炸 - 下车
- Motherfucker's gonna blow! - Get the fuck out!
这算在你杀人的帐上吗?
Should I add this to your body count?
毒品线索没了
There goes our only lead to the dope.
够惨吧?
Ain't this a bitch?
毒品?
"The dope"?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
如果说"杀人凶手跑了"是 不是好点?
How about there goes our only lead to Max's killer?
他还逍遥法外
He's still out there.
那不重要
But that's not really important.
反正你们不是来保护人的
It's not like it's your job to protect people. Holy shit.
- 看吧? 她疯了吧 - 我疯了?
- She's crazy. - I'm crazy?
她疯了
- You're gone! - I'm out of here!
怎么了? 闭嘴 她是证人
- What is wrong with you ? Stop! - She done fucking zoomed!
她疯了 就这样 你去跟她谈
- This is the witness! - That's it. You deal with her.
不必 我
- No way. - Listen.
好 你说对了
- Bullshit. - Yes, you're right.
起因是毒品被窃 但我告诉你
This started because of missing drugs, but let me tell you something.
对麦克来说没有任何事…
There is absolutely nothing more important to Mike...
…比找到杀玛克丝的 凶手更重要
than doing this guy that killed Max.
有时他很难流露他真正的想法
I know he has a hard time expressing his feelings.
来吧 没事的?
Come on. It will be all right, okay?
我们需要你
We need you.
你是我们的同伴
Part of the team.
我以为温柔的该是他
I thought he was supposed to be the smooth one.
今天够糟的
- This has not been a good day. - Damn right. This is bullshit.
没错 糟透了 剩两天要找到那些笨蛋…
We got two days to find these fools...
…而我们断了线了因为 你在路上杀了诺尔
and we got no leads because you cooked Noah's ass on the freeway.
有洗发精吗?
- Shampoo? - Hello.
嗨
- There. - Let's do that.
什么事?
What's up?
买洗发精不需要要那么久
It don't take that long to get shampoo.
- 走吧 - 看这个
- Please, let's go. - Look at this.
"动物实验 动物实验"
"Animal tested."
你知道这里面有多少化学物质?
Do you know how many chemicals are in this stuff?
就算你头秃了也不要紧 快走
I don't care if you go bald. Just get it and let's go.
他是个化学家
He is a chemist.
有太多的海洛因
That's entirely too much heroin and too much ether...
大家一定 会知道些的
for nobody to know nothing.
你在说什么?
What is he talking about?
记得在卡车上爆炸的乙醚吗?
You know the barrels of ether that blew up on the ice cream truck?
是他们用来加工海洛因的
They were going to use that to process the heroin.
加上它 价值可增加四倍
Yeah, they do that to cut it. It quadruples the value.
不能就这样放进微波炉
Yeah, you can't just stick it in the microwave.
付钱吧
Maybe you're onto something. Let's just pay for this, all right?
- 多少? - $14.25元
- How much is that? - Fourteen twenty-five.
我皮夹忘了掉在哪
Damn. I must have left my wallet somewhere.
别动 混蛋 别动
Freeze, mother bitches! Don't you move.
- 我不懂 - 闭嘴
- I'm not understanding. I really don't. - Shut up!
- 你是暴力吸引者吗? - 别紧张
- Do you just attract violent people? - Take it easy, all right?
- 我们是警察 - 你们才不是
- We are police officers. - You're not police officers.
我不笨 我了解的 我见过警察
- I'm not stupid. I've seen police. - What are you?
- 我拿警徽给你看 可以吗? - 你要警徽? 混蛋?
- I'm going to reach for my badge. - You want badges, mother bitch?
我给你警徽
I give you badges! Here!
这儿 9毛9一个 卖给你些
Ninety-nine cents each! I sell you some!
你有八个警徽 早跟你说这招不管用
You got eight badges! I told you this cop thing don't work.
我轰了你 再轰你
I blow you ! Then I blow you!
轰我? 你奸了我吧 那没关系的
Blow me? What the fuck? Hump me. That's all right.
我可是杀过人的
I'm from the Middle East! I kill before. I kill again!
- 等等 - 我会轰掉你 - 奸我吧 - 等等
- Fuck me, please! Hold on! - No, you hold on!
你知道我现在的感觉吗?
Do you see the emotion I'm going through now?
这表示情势似乎颇严重的
That means this shit is serious.
这表示我和这混蛋不能沟通
Me and this mother fucker's not vibing right now. That's what that means.
- 你要说什么? - 我有话
- You got something on your chest? - That's what I'm saying!
- 喂 他拿的是巨炮耶 - 你想干嘛?
- Hello? The guy has got a cannon. - What do you want?
想打架? 来呀
- Do you want some? Come get some. - I want some!
- 我走了 - 别动 贱人
- I'm gone. - Freeze, bitch!
- 你别动 贱人 - 完了 我死定了
- You freeze, bitch! - Oh, shit. I'm fucked.
退后 放下枪
Now back up, put the gun down...
给我一包口香糖
and give me a pack of Tropical Fruit Bubblicious.
还有水果糖
And some Skittles.
累毙了 我要睡了
Hell of a night. I'm going to bed.
请你别客气 床是你的
So make your self at home. It's your bed.
我先…坐一下
I'll sit down for a minute...
我在保卫你
'cause I'm guarding shit, you know.
以免坏人来骚扰
I'm watching out for the bad boys.
我能从我直觉…
I can see things, you know...
…观察出事物
real well from my "peripheals."
这么个帅哥…
You know, for such a stud, Mike Lowrey...
…你好像很不习惯有 女孩在你的床上
you sure seem a little rigid about having a girl in your bed.
谁? 我? 麦克拉瑞?
Who? Me? Mike Lowrey?
才不会 我很舒服
I'm not rigid. I'm comfortable.
这是我的床
This is my bed.
- 怎会紧张? - 我不懂
- Why would I be uncomfortable? - I don't know.
感觉好奇怪,大概是因为太刺激了
I think it's more than just wired. Maybe it was all the guns and stuff.
我以前没开过枪 所有的事…
I've never really shot a gun before, and that's... All that steel.
我觉得 你不觉得蛮好玩的?
I'm feeling... Don't you feel a little funny?
我不是喜剧演员 我不是说那种好玩
- I'm not a comedian, but... - I don't mean that kind of funny.
我是说…好笑
I mean like funny.
你不会想要那样的
Now, you don't want that.
你不是真想 如果我来的时候…
'Cause when I come...
…我像闪电一样的 而且那是…
I come with the thunder.
你像怕被老婆发现似的
You sound like you're saving your self for marriage.
我才不是 那是马可士
That ain't me. That's Marcus.
你知道我在说什么吗? 他才怕老婆发现
You know what I'm saying? He's the married one.
还有别的 不
I got some other... Oh, no.
我看完了 翻过去
I've seen it now. Turn the page, girl.
别笑
Don't laugh.
没想到他黑人头这么大
I cannot believe he wore his Afro that big.
- 我忘了 - 他那样很可爱
- I forgot all about that. - I think he looked cute like that.
马可士老婆如何?
What's Marcus's wife like?
就是老婆嘛
She's like a wife.
能栓住像马可士一样的 男人一定很不得了
I mean, she must be pretty amazing to keep a guy like Marcus.
- 怎样的男人? - 今晚我看他的表现…
- Keep a guy like what? - Like watching him tonight...
…他很能掌握情势
He's very sort of take-charge.
他把人弄得那样服贴
The way he was throwing guys this way and that.
他有种我无法形容的特质
There's something about him. I don't know what it is.
他好温柔
He's so smooth, you know?
天哪…我敢说…
Boy, I bet his wife's...
…他老婆现在正享受他的 温柔
enjoying the smoothness right this minute.
- 他有女人爱的特质 - 当然
- He's got a quality women respond to. - Sure.
我想没有哪个女人…
I can't imagine the kind of woman...
…不为马可士著迷的
that wouldn't find Marcus attractive.
不能跟他…
Probably couldn't be around him and just...
…像我们一样在一起 像是两人独处
You know, like our situation.
那种男人不可能
- If two people were alone... - Not with a guy like that.
对不起
Excuse me.
- 怎么了? - 这张上过布告栏
What is wrong with him? This one goes on the bulletin board at work.
别这样 不要嘛
Uh-uh. Don't do that.
放回来 我不相信你抽出去了
Putitback in. I cannot be lieve you took it out.
马可士知道会宰了我 给我吧
Come on. Marcus will kill us if he finds out. Give it to me.
没想到让你看了
I can't be lieve I let you see it.
王八蛋
Motherfucker!
妈的
Goddamn it.
为你买了些首饰 对不起 但没办法
Got some jewelry for you . I'm sorry, but damn that.
我们的关系…似乎存在绝对的不信任
I think we need to address the serious lack of trust in this relationship.
- 拜托 - 这合法吗? 我不觉得这是合法的
- Please. - I don't think this is legal.
- 我马上来 - 这是合法的 别让人看见
I won't be long. It's legal. Out of sight.
山契斯 我是拉瑞 妈的 听好
Sanchez, this is Lowrey. Yeah, your mother. Listen.
那些人将有行动
These guys are about to make a move.
蓝色双座敞蓬车 查一下
Blue convertible, two visible occupants. Check it out, all right?
来了
Here we go.
- 是他吗? - 对
- Is that our guy? - That's him.
那女的呢? 我没看见有女孩
- Where's the girl? - I don't see any girl. There's no girl.
烂狗 鬼叫鬼叫 闭嘴
Fuck off, barking-ass dog. Shut up.
偷爬自己家
Sneak up on my own house.
怎么回事? 很奇怪
What in the world? Very strange.
他在楼上 还说是我兄弟
His ass upstairs. Supposed to be my boy.
王八蛋
You motherfucker.
扭扭乐 爽歪歪
Ducking and weaving up and down.
你看 这是你要的?
Look at this shit. Is this what you want?
让我像只猩猩爬来
Got me climbing like a chimp.
没那么容易打发我
But I ain't going out like that.
上床不需要这么久的
It don't take anybody that long to get into bed.
跟我宝贝在家
Got my babies in the house.
我都没品味的时光…
Your man can't get no quality time...
…我兄弟倒有
but my partner can get some quality time.
想得美
I don't play that shit.
- 有人在外面 - 去保护小孩
- There's somebody out there. - Quick, get the kids.
我早就知道了 不必打给灵媒
I knew it! I didn't have to call the fucking psychic line!
别动
Freeze!
敢动你就死
- Move and you're a dead man! - Motherfucker!
他们互相拼命 真不可思议
Gun up to his head. They're going to shoot each other. Unbelievable.
- 警察 别动 - 我是警察 我是
- Miami Police! Freeze! - I am the police!
- 马克士 你在干嘛? - 你在干泰莉莎
- Marcus, what are you doing? - You're doing Theresa!
- 没有 - 你在干我的宝贝
- I'm not! - Nobody does my baby!
- 闭嘴 现在可以干掉他俩
We could sneak up and snuff them both right now.
目标是那女的
Yeah, but we're supposed to get the girl. Forget them.
别管条子家务事
Never fuck with a cop's family, asshole.
- 那不会让你生气吗? - 没错
- Doesn't that piss you off? - That pisses the fuck out of me.
少惹我 下车
Don't get me started. Get out of the car.
妈的 你疯啦
Fuck it! Some shit is making you crazy.
我没跟泰莉莎怎样
You know there's nothing going on between me and Theresa!
我们六年同事…
Man, I've been your partner for six years...
…一辈子的交情
and I've been your boy all my life.
但你都不想…
For you to even think...
…我怎会做那种事
To let some dumb shit like that creep up in your mind...
是我呀 你怎么了?
This is me! What is wrong with you?
干…
It was just... I don't know.
我只是…
I just...
没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
快走吧 茱莉呢?
Get the fuck out of here. Where's Julie?
在车上 被铐在方向盘上
She's in the car, handcuffed to the steering wheel.
你想搞砸案子吗?
Are you trying to blow this case?
我的错 我都没"品味时光"
My bad, man. I ain't had no quality time.
你知道你是怎么回事 你老做傻事
You know how that is. Sometimes you do dumb shit.
就是这样而已
- Let's go. - That's all that is.
我错了
Yo, my bad.
没事了
It's cool.
走吧
Go. All right. Yeah.
这些电话是从局里
These calls were made to Club Hell...
打去地狱酒店
from this precinct.
请解释
Explain.
再问你一次 谁是你老大
I'll ask you one more time. Give me a goddamn name!
- 我只知他名字 - 告诉我
- All I know is his name. - Give me his name.
否则就进大牢 知道吗?
You're looking at a lot of time. You know that?
傅谢 大概是傅谢
Fouchet, I think.
是全名吗? 傅谢?
That's his whole name?
我只是个小弟
I'm just an errand boy.
别这样 我会哭
Stop it, please. You're gonna make me cry.
我发誓 我只负责看门
I swear, watching the house was my first gig.
很好 那你也是一伙的了?
How sweet. Does that make you union?
若你是实际办案…每天工作的条子…
If you were a real cop in the field working every day...
…你就了解倒楣事可多了
you'd realize that sometimes shit happens.
少来这套 你要被调职了
Don't give me that crap. You're on your way to being reassigned.
我要被调职了? 谁调我职? 你?
- Shut down soon. - Who will reassign me? You?
你还无权调我职
You don't have the authority to reassign me.
直到那时候…一边凉快吧
Until you do, stay the hell out of here!
他们应该快点解决这事
They should just bone and get that shit over with.
我真的很讨厌被铐
I'm getting really tired of this.
你讨厌?
You're tired?
这些烂人不干活了 太懒了 得用监视器
These guard dogs aren't cutting it. They're overfed. They're lazy.
那些警卫狗不算什么
We need video surveillance 'cause these guard dogs are nothing...
别让我们为难
Jo jo. Don't make this hard!
真高兴又见面 乔乔
Nice running into you.
总是跟你自己过不去
Always making it hard on your self.
茱莉 你在干嘛?
Gee, Julie, what have you been up to the last couple days?
没什么 只是成天逛逛 没事就被铐在方向盘上
Nothing. Just hanging out, handcuffed to steering wheels.
我们在找加工毒品的人
We're looking for someone who can step on a shit load of heroin.
又快又好 真的行家
Do it real fast, real well. We're looking for a real pro.
我说过我只搞轮胎了
I told you already, I'm in the rubber business now.
乔乔 我们不是在跟你玩
Jo jo, we're not playing.
我说过我不搞毒品
I'm straight, man.
我真的没搞毒品
I'm straight like a board, like an arrow.
我真的没搞毒品 我快吐了
I'm so straight right now, I'm sick.
那么多毒品 谁能快速加工?
It's a lot of dope. Who could cut it real quick?
加工? 你是说混合?
"Cut it"? You cut it up?
我恨透了这胡说八道
- I don't know nothing about it. - I'm so sick of this bullshit.
- 怎么了? - 你拿枪对著我?
- What's up? - You're pulling a gun on me?
你们是条子 我要投诉到电视台
You guys are cops! I can't believe this! I should turn you in to Hard Copy.
- 让你上电视 - 你在做什么?
- Put your ass on the TV set! - What are you doing?
- 让我来 我有15颗子弹
I got this! I got 15 bullets in this gun.
你再不说 我就喂你吃子弹
Lf you don't start talking to me, I'll fill your ass full of hot shit.
他只是一个曾吸毒的屁蛋,他不值得
- Now, what's up? - Mike, he ain't worth it!
你要吃吗? 我也喂你几颗
Do you want some? I'll bust your ass too!
可惜呀 我帮不了你了
So sad. You're on your own, Jojo.
- 怎么了? - 我这样告诉你…
- What's up? - I'm telling you like this.
…你轰他对咱们没好处
You splatter his ass, he's no good to us!
- 去死吧 - 我可不想因这被捕
Fuck that. I'm not going down over this shit!
我可不想因你杀个卖轮胎的
I'm not going down for you killing Jojo the tire man!
我不想让脑浆弄脏衣服
I don't want no brain fragments on me!
那味道会沾上衣服而且很臭
That shit gets in your clothes, and it stinks!
干
- Fuck that! - I'll tell you what I know.
我不是全都知道 只有一点
I don't know everything. I know a little bit.
跟他说一点吧
Tell him something!
有三个人 他们有个实验室
It's three guys. They got a laboratory...
不 不 是两个人
No, it's two guys.
一个去年死于空难
One guy died in a plane crash last year. It was fucked up.
以前还更多
There should be more! Fuck, man!
不 是一个人 只有一个人
It's one guy, really. It's only one guy.
别骗我
- Don't fuck with me. - One main guy.
他是天才大学生…
This guy's an Einstein, motherfucking genius college boy.
…绝顶聪明 戴眼镜
Egghead motherfucker. He got four eyes and glasses.
他的阔绰父母住椰林
He got a rich mama and daddy who live out in Coconut Grove.
哪里? 再说一次 乔乔
Where? Tell him again, Jojo!
我告诉你地点
- I don't want you to get hurt! - I'll tell you where he's at.
- 你会这么做? - 我要帮你们
- You would do that for us? - Yeah, I want to help you guys.
你放下枪
You stick that gun down.
我去…办公室…拿地址
I got the address in the office.
谢谢 请去拿吧?
Thanks a lot. You go grab that.
好
- Cool. - You can go ahead.
- 去 - 现在? 现在很好 现在真的很好
- Now? - Now is real good.
我免费提供
Yeah. This is on me too.
你可以选个轮胎 算我送的
You guys pick out some whitewalls as a little gift from me to you.
我以为你真要轰我
You made me think you would shoot me for a minute.
我是打算
I was.
这痞子几时回家?
When is this punk-ass chemist coming home?
埋伏就是这样 不像我想的
So this is a stakeout. Not what I imagined.
我以为要讲很久
Thought there would be more conversation.
抱歉 这不符合你的…普通的高水准
Sorry it's not up to your usual high standards.
他在埋伏的时候老这样吗?
Is he always like this on a stakeout?
干嘛? 咖啡因中毒呀? 性生活不美满?
Too much caffeine? Not enough sex?
我不相信她这样说你
I can't believe she went there on you.
你不知道你在跟谁说话? 他是麦克拉瑞
You know who you're talking to? That's Mike Lowrey over there.
天赋异"柄"
King Ding-a-ling.
拿出来给她瞧?
Why don't you whip it out for her, big boy?
太长了不好拿
Uh-huh. Right on your forehead.
闭嘴
- Shut up. - Yeah.
- 他来了 - 走 - 我去跟他
- There he is! Let's go! Move! - I'm on him!
机会有多少?
What are our chances?
记得地狱酒店吧? 比那更糟
Remember Club Hell? Worse.
好了 请求所有的支援
That's it. I'm calling major backup.
小猫小狗也要来
- I want swimming ducks in here. - Whoa.
等一下 辛克莱装了窃听器
Hold it. You know Sinclair has every phone in the station tapped.
我们要自给自足
- We have to do that in person. - Shit.
到那个时候…
By the time we deal with her bullshit...
…所有毒贩都跑光了
every junkie in America will be high off our bust.
你要干嘛?
Can we help you?
我整晚坐在车里
I staked out all night in that jalopy too.
我想偷看一下
I think I earned a peek.
现在是来真的 不是"查理的天使"
This is real cop stuff. This is not Charlie's Angels.
偷看一下不会怎样
It can't hurt for her to take a peek.
看一下没关系? 万一子弹 飞来可就疼了
It can't hurt to look? If they fire a bullet over here, it will hurt.
有客人了 跟踪他们
We have guests. Have them followed.
别做任何事 通知我他们的位置
Don't do anything. Just call me with their location.
一场飞车追杀
This high-speed chase endingona trestle...
在34街和桥头结束
near the RiverDrive and 34th Street intersection...
…这是记者两天前所拍
was captured twonights ago b your 6Action News team.
妈
Mom!
你说爸在克里夫兰
I thought you said Daddy was in Cleveland.
不可能
He can't be in Cleveland.
两名警官不喜欢我们拍摄
The officers didn't like the presence of our camera.
他只是希望在克里夫兰
Your daddy just wishes he was in Cleveland.
我跟你说 这个傅谢狡滑的很
I'm telling you . This Fouchet is a slick one.
调查局 药物管理局都没他资料
FBI, DEA... They got nothing on him.
但他今天要会会咱们
But he has to deal with us today.
这是什么?
What's that?
是最后一次铐我了. 就是那个意思
That's the last time they handcuff me. That's what that is.
好狗狗
Good boy.
对不起 女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
所有的访客都要登记
All visitors must be announced!
我生气了
Pisses me off. Lady!
小姐 小姐
I guess when you guys get back...
你们回来后一切就结束了吧?
this will all be over, right?
没错 放心
You got that right. Don't worry, though.
你会被释放 不戴手铐了
You'll be set free, cut loose.
你会回到你原来的生活
You'll be back to your old life.
没手铐了
Oops. No more handcuffs.
- 我走了 - 查特拿我的
- Get up out of here. - That should be Chet...
素汉堡来了
with my veggie burger.
- 快点 - 好嘛
- Move your ass! - You got it.
有什么事?
Hi. Can I help you?
我来宰我老公马可士
Yes, I'm here to kill my husband, Marcus Burnett.
高的还是矮的?
And that would be the tall one or the short one?
- 矮的 - 我早料到
- The short one. - Thought so.
是查特在按?
Is Chet ringing the...
宝贝
Baby...
- 我去叫你老公 - 过来
- Let me get your husband. - Marcus, get over here.
因为我知道这看起来像什么 你没接到我留话吗?
I'm a... I know what it looks like. Did you get my message?
麻烦你…让我和…伯纳太太谈话好吗?
Can you leave me and Mrs. Burnett alone for...
好
Right.
你们都见过了吗? ?
Y'all met?
宝贝…
Baby...
…我知道 让我
I know, so let me...
我觉得 你可以把婚戒放在 口袋里…
As far as I'm concerned, you can keep the wedding ring in your pocket...
…因为你和你女友
because you , your new little girlfriend...
噢 妈的
Shit.
- 和麦克可以快乐地住这里
And Mike will all be very happy living here.
- 相信我 - 甜心 甜心
- Trust me. - Sweetie... Honey...
我在电视上看见你们
I saw it on the news.
电视歪曲事实
- That shit be having a slant. - It's...
你不必回家了
- You're no longer welcome in my house. - He didn't tell you ...
他没说我提早下飞机?
I was coming in the airport early?
叫你打电话 你还带我来这?
Remember I said call her? Hold on.
告诉她我跟你说过的呀?
Tell her what I told you.
你要带我去你的
You were gonna bring me to your place...
我不是要…
All right. I ain't even gonna...
我们没吵
We're not arguing about this.
我在大声说 好 宝贝…
I'm raising my... All right, here... Baby...
我们早就想告诉你的
Believe me, we wanted to tell you.
那不重要 马克士 麦克
It really doesn't matter anymore, Marcus...
不管你叫什么
Mike. Kojak. Whatever your name is.
让我告诉你
Aside from that fact, I'll tell you something else.
如果他的老婆都找得到我们 我还是自己逃命吧
If his wife could find us, I'm a lot better off on my own.
这… 我知道这整个情况看起来是这样
This... I could see how it would look a trip.
你看到的 我跑出去然后衬衫 打开了
You see me run out. I got a shirt open.
麦克半裸著
You see Mike half-butt-naked.
然后你看见女人
Then you see the white girl.
好像我们在杂交 其实没人在玩
So this looks like we having one big orgy here, and ain't nobody humping.
没人在干那事
Ain't nobody doing none of that.
不是你想的那样 听到我说的吧
It's not what it looks like. Hear what I'm saying.
宝贝 她是证人
Baby, she's a material witness.
真的
- That... - That's real!
宝贝 泰莉莎 听著
Baby, listen. That ain't...
那是命令 是命令
It was orders, baby.
我能跟你谈谈吗?
Can I talk to you?
停下来听我说行吗?
Can you stop so I can talk to you , please?
少来你哄人那套 没用了
Enough with the smooth shit, Mike. It won't work anymore.
我不在乎
I don't care what you say.
- 趴下 - 茱莉 趴下
- Duck! - Julie, get down now!
趴下 出去
- Get out, now! - Mike, help!
拨119
911!
119? 我是查特
Yeah, 911? Chet here.
上楼 这个拿著 拿著
Go upstairs and take this. Take it!
放心 支援到以前 我会让大家冷静
Don't worry. I'll keep everybody calm until my backup arrives.
我爱你
I love you.
忘了说地址
Shit! I forgot to give them the address!
走
Come on! Move!
小心
Go! Watch it!
继续走
- Keep going! - Son of a bitch!
让她进来
Get her in!
走
Move!
没事 我是警察
It's okay. I'm with the police.
一切没事 你们很美
It's cool. You look great.
开车 开车
Drive!
别说我没救过你
Don't ever say I wasn't there for you.
你是怎么回事?
What is it with you guys?
为什么总是有好消息跟坏消息?
How come it's always good news, bad news?
你知道毒品下落 但丢了证人
You know exactly where the dope is, but you lose our only witness.
- 我真不懂 - 听电话
- I just don't get it. - Pick up your phone.
我要留著你的朋友四小时 直到我交易完成
I'm keeping your sweet little friend for four hours until I make my deal.
我会让交易完成
And I will make my deal.
我刚杀了…
I've just put a bullet in the chemist...
…不听话的化学家
who fucked with my timetable.
下面就轮到这女孩 知道吗?
The other one is for the girl. Okay?
王八蛋
Son of a bitch!
他杀了他手下
Twisted motherfucker just shot one of his employees.
若我们不放弃 他就杀茱莉
Said if we don't back off, he'll kill Julie.
- 没时间 - 我叫你照法规办事
- Not now. - I told you to play by the rules.
我就快破案了
I am on the verge of solving this case!
你把南沙滩变成战场
You turned South Beach into a war zone.
这是命令 停止侦办此案 你们全调职了
I finally got the authority to shut you down. You're all reassigned.
这真好 妈的王八
This is lovely.
这家伙把我逼急了
This guy is painting me into a corner.
他会杀了她 我不会让她死的
He'll kill the girl anyway, and we're won't let her die.
我们不退让 不管她说什么
We're not walking away from this bust, I don't care what she says.
买卖在四小时后开始
The deal goes down in four hours.
表示你在两小时内要找到他们
You guys have two hours to find them.
得靠点运气了
It's time to get lucky.
做你们该做的
Go do what you have to do.
傅莱彻 你说这可以快一点的
Fletcher, you told us this would move a little quicker than this.
没那么容易 如果是这么简单 你自己都可以来做
It's not that easy, okay? If it was, you'd be doing it.
你说你是电脑天才
Work your magic. You say you're a computer whiz. Come on.
少废话 我帮你们违法办事
Back up off me. I'm doing an illegal favor for you.
我就是这样被关的
This is what I got put in jail for.
别再逼我
So you back up off me.
如果你不坐下…
You don't sit your lanky ass down... bottom line...
…否则我就扁你
I will knock you the fuck out!
- 怎么了? - 坐下
- What the fuck is wrong with you ? - Can you have a seat?
- 你说会放我出牢 - 我没骗你的
- You said you'd get me out of jail. - I wasn't lying.
警察真笨 你看
Cops are so dumb. Look, it's coming up.
记住你要释放我
Remember, you promised to get me out.
艾迪多明哥
这就是了 找到了
There is it. Voila.
- 唐妮 法兰欣 - "女友"?
"Girlfriend"?
除夕时 我前男友艾…
It was New Year's Eve and my ex-boyfriend, Eddie...
…和这法国人…
and this French guy...
…拍了我裸照
took some really horrible pictures of me.
他们说…他们会把照片…
They said they would put them on the bulletin board...
…放在我儿子学校公布栏…
of my kid's school...
…若不给他们毒品资料
unless I gave them a lot of narcotics information.
但我从未把你和女孩的…资料给他
But I never gave them you or the girl!
她被抓走 我们要找到他们
Look, they got the girl. We need to get them now.
如果我们不这么做她就会死
Because if we don't, they'll kill her.
- 你怎么联络他们? - 我有他手机电话
- How do you make contact? - I have their mobile phone number.
我很抱歉 我会弥补你
I'm sorry. Listen, I'll make it up to you.
我会的 我会做任何事的
I'll do anything you want.
没时间了 走吧
We don't have a lot of time. Let's go.
你耳朵很性感 知道吗?
You have sexy ears. You know that?
我想舔一舔
I want to lick them.
罗密欧在吗?
- Yeah? - Can I speak to Romeo?
这里没这人 白痴
There ain't no Romeo here, asshole.
你在笑谁?
Why are you laughing?
这电话可一直追踪他
This cell phone will triangulate him...
无论他到哪里
no matter where he goes.
等他停车就注意地图
We'll watch on this map until he stops.
信号还很强 我们还找得到他们
- Sector234. - The signal is still strong.
走吧 宝贝
- We still have a lock. - We got them.
谢了
- Come on, baby. - Thank you.
露西最棒 仔细想一想
Lucywas the queen, baby. Think about it.
她是白痴嘛
Lucille Ball was a bimbo. What are you talking about?
- 代西是幕后主脑 - 什么话?
- Desi was the brains. - How could you say that?
- 什么意思? - 没有小鼓 他就没看头
- What do you mean? - Without those bongos, he's nothing.
是康鼓
It's conga. Don't be so stupid. It's Desi and Lucy...
弟兄 怎样?
Yo, what's up?
你们这些烂人
The fucking pencil squad.
我们在指挥交通吗?
Did you get us assigned to traffic duty?
- 这回有大事 有任务给你们 - 可能会送命
- This is real. We got something for you. - This shit could get you killed.
走吧
Let's go.
来了
Here we go.
我是康洛 你帮我个忙
It's Conrad. I'm calling in a favor.
东向第135街行进
Eastbound towards northwest 135th Street.
东北方 走东北方
Keep going northeast.
要是我错了就开除我
If I'm wrong about this, you can fire my ass.
我需要以下支援
This is what I need.
特训小组 直升机
I need a SWAT team, helicopters...
所有能出动的警力 但还不知去哪支援
We're calling all cars, baby. Only I don't know where I need them.
- 好车 - 对呀 这是我的玩具
- Very nice car you got there. - Yeah. That's my toy.
我要当成收集品
I'm taking it with me, for my collection.
钱汇出去没?
How about the wire transfers?
有两笔先汇入你银行…
Two wire transfers to your banks...
…一共18亿美元
totaling $180 million.
有二千万现金
And 20 in cash.
妈的
Damn.
这星期简直够倒楣
This has been a shitty week.
找到目标 收到讯号
Getting full integration on that signal.
我们到飞机场了
Yeah, we're on the airfield now.
一定在机库那边
I bet you it's up in the old hangar section.
就在这 拿上来 捡起来
Go ahead. Bring it up.
请确认存款
Deposit confirmation requested.
九千万苏黎士银行
90 million, Geldersbank of zurich.
不好进去
No easy approach.
没时间等支援了
No time. Fuck the backup.
- 现在就得走 - 没问题
- We have to go now. - Not a problem.
- 你痒吗? 我很想帮你搔痒 - 搔这个
- Got an itch? I'd love to scratch it. - Scratch this.
- 要我搔哪都行 你这蓝眼睛婊子 - 你念过大学吗?
- I'll scratch whatever you want, blue eye bitch. - Did you go to college?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 确定要这么干? - 走
- You sure you want to do this? - Let's go.
把裙子塞进去
Tuck in your skirt, baby. Come on!
我点子一向灵
My shit always works sometimes!
这是最棒的货 很高兴和你交易
This is the best you can buy. It's been nice doing business with you.
妈的
Shit.
这是陷阱
It's a setup!
我死了就拖你下水
If I get killed, I'm fucking you up!
妈的 快
Goddamn it, go.
老天
My God!
趴下
Get down!
你忘了登机证
You forgot your boarding pass.
王八蛋
You motherfuckers!
- 怎么了? - 干
- What's up? - Shit!
- 我们走 - 上车
- Mike, let's go! - Shit! Get in the car!
上车 麦克 快
Get in! Come on!
上来 这玩意要爆了
This shit's gonna blow!
起来
Get up!
妈的 去追那个射伤我的人
Shit! Please catch that motherfucker!
他射你 他射我
- Hes hot me. - Hes hot you ? Hes hot me.
- 你没事吧? - 还好 只是跟
- You all right? - Just had a little run-in...
足球员跑了一圈
with your friend Jim Brown, but I'm fine.
他偷了我们毒品 绑架茱莉 对我老婆开枪
He steals our shit, kidnaps Julie, shoots at my wife.
干掉他
We beating him down!
马可士 我问你个问题
Marcus, I just got one question for you , bro.
你怎么不救我 先去开车?
How the hell you leave my ass at a gunfight to go get the car?
闭嘴让他开车
You have got to shut up and let him drive!
被人射杀过之后 车开的也比较好了
Seems like that gunshot wound has improved your driving skills.
你有权保持缄默
You got the right to remain silent.
你说的话将作为呈堂证供
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
- 你干嘛? - 一定要说出来
- What are you doing? - Getting it out of the way.
加油 追上他
Just punch it, man! Go!
- 万一他的车快呢? - 不会
This car's faster! This is a faster car!
不是他毁就是我们毁了
It's one or the other, baby! It's him or it's us!
最好赢他
You better fucking win, that's all I know!
要赢呀
You better win!
这才叫开车
Now that's how you supposed to drive!
从现在起 你就这么开车
From now on, that's how you drive!
别动
Freeze!
不值得杀他
He ain't even worth killing.
我打赌你一早醒来绝没想到…
I bet when your punk ass woke up this morning...
…下午五点腿上多个洞
you didn't think about 5:00 you'd have a hole in your leg.
你不能杀我吧 胆小鬼 能吗?
You couldn't kill me, you chicken shit, could you?
我可以 你好像以为结束了
I could. You're talking like it's over.
我只是暂停一下
I was just pausing.
我开始喜欢当狙击家了
I'm starting to get the hang of this marksman shit.
30码之外射中跑的人 不算什么
Shooting them from 30 yards while they're running away is not it.
这才是 零距离射才叫厉害
Here's where it is, right here. Point-blank, up close and personal.
这就是我的意思
That's what I'm talking about.
你会这么做?
Would you do it?
退一步
Mike, step off.
开枪
Do it.
结束了
It's over.
他是个笑话 是个他妈的大笑话
He's a joke. He's a motherfuckin'joke.
我说过我爱你吗?
I ever tell you I love you , man?
你每次枪战后 就变得多愁善感
Yeah, you always be getting emotional after gunfights.
没死很开心
It's 'cause I'm glad we survived.
妈的
Shit.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
我也爱你
I love you too, man.
别看我 我说了我爱你
Don't be looking at me. I said, "I love you ."
- 我说了那屁话 - 你是我兄弟
- I said that shit. - You my boy, man!
不 你像我兄弟
No, you like my brother, man.
那我是什么?
So what am I?
- 噢 老天 - 茱莉 甜心…
- Man... - Julie, sweetie, you ...
你有点危险
You're a little dangerous.
你是枪战的大磁铁
Yeah, you're like a magnet for random gunfire.
但你不错 你很酷
But you're all right. You're cool.
你很好
You down.
那下一步呢?
So what's next?
没有…下一步了
See, there ain't gonna be no next.
嘿 干什么
Whoa, Marcus. Come on.
你喜欢麦克拉瑞…交给你
You wanted Mike Lowrey. You got him.
这是麦克 麦克拉瑞
Right here. That's Mike. Old Mike Lowrey.
我要回家找"品味时光"
I'm going home to my wife to get my quality time.
别闹了 兄弟?
Marcus, stop playing, man.
我被扁三次
I been beat three times since we been out here.
我没事 不必帮我 退后
I'm cool man. I don't need help. Please, back up.
回家找老婆干嘛?
Why are you going home to your wife?
你腿中枪 老二可能没用了
You got shot in the leg. Your dick probably don't work.
你有钥匙吗?
Marcus, do you have the keys?
麦克要我去个枪战…
Mike wanted me to go to this gunfight.
然后还有一个证人…
Then there was this witness.
兄弟 对不起 对不起
My man! Sorry.
- 放开我吧 - 我没钥匙
- Can you let me out of here? - I don't have the keys.
你没有钥匙吗? 你为什么没钥匙?
What do you mean? Why wouldn't you have keys?